Grockbot is one of the most powerful AI
tools that I've ever played with because
it gives you an army of AI agents right
in your pocket and you don't have to be
technical at all to use it and to get
value out of it. I've been playing
around with Grockbot since it came out
and it has actually changed the way that
I'm working rather than just being like
a fun AI tool, a bunch of agents that's
just good for like a demo or for social
media. So, in this video, I'm going to
break down everything that you need to
know about Grockbot. I'm going to show
you the way I'm using it. I'm going to
do a full setup. I'm going to talk about
the mindset and how you actually connect
this stuff so it becomes useful. I'm
going to be spinning up a completely new
account and building out a team of
agents right here in front of you guys.
So, you can basically just follow along.
And I'm going to be showing you how you
can use it to obviously provide value to
you and to grow your business, but also
how this is a really good offer to go
into other businesses with and help them
get set up with their own Grockbots. And
real quick, if you guys don't know me,
my name is Nate. I've been building AI
automations and agents for about 2 years
now. I've got a global community of AI
builders that's over 440,000 members.
And my business in the past 12 months
has done just under $5 million of
topline revenue. And it's because
everyone's able to move quicker because
of using systems like these. And that's
across things like education,
communities, certifications, events,
newsletters, and more. So anyways, by
the end of this course, you'll be
completely set up with what you need to
know about Grockbot and scaling your
business and other businesses. So let's
not waste any time and just get straight
into this one. Okay, so Grockbot, it's
AI teammates that you can give real work
to and they can sign in, they can use
your tools, and they can take action for
you. You can see that you're going to
get a nice interface that's sort of like
a Telegram style thing, so it feels very
familiar and you're able to talk to them
like teammates. They can talk to each
other. They can delegate work to each
other. They can do things while you
sleep. It's super super cool. And just
to start off with like a 30,000 foot
view and to see where we're going in
this course, I'm obviously going to sign
out of this, spin up a new account, and
set up everything with you guys so
you're not confused at all. But this is
kind of what this could look like by the
end of this course for you. So, right
here, you can see that I have a group
chat. This is actually a channel similar
to like you have Slack channels or
ClickUp channels or whatever you're used
to. And you can see that on the left I
basically have DMs with all of my
different agents whether they're general
or their content or the ones that I've
pinned up here which is kind of like my
seuite. My executive assistant I call
them chief. I've got my COO, my CCO
which I call a chief content officer and
then my CFO. So anyways, what we're
looking at right here is I have these
four agents in a group chat called
leadership. And what I said is based on
how this past week has gone and our
long-term goals, I want you guys to
ideulate. I want you guys to help me
figure out what should we be doing in
the fourth quarter? How do we continue
to differentiate? and how do we continue
to reduce keyman risk as we keep scaling
up the business? So, you can see that
they come together, Becky, Dan,
Chandler, and Klouse all come together
and talk about the different areas that
they're involved in, and they work
together like a leadership team to help
me figure out what we need to be doing.
They're tagging each other, they're
talking to each other, they're reading
each other's answers. And then right
here, they finally came down to five key
decisions that they agreed on, which was
no new business units in Q4, spend only
to get Nate off the critical paths,
second phase test off on the main
channel, Becky owns comment mind pick,
so Nate isn't the idea gate, and CIC is
the 2027 unit that scales without Nate
on camera. So, obviously, there's more
here to dig into, but that is what they
were able to come up with in just a few
minutes based on their areas of
expertise in my business. And the reason
why I have these four main agents pinned
up here is because what's going to
happen is as you start to use Grockbot,
you're going to spin up a ton of
different agents. You can see that I
mean I only have 10 right now in here,
which isn't actually that many, but I
have each agent having one very specific
purpose. This one just looks at X. This
one just creates animations. This one
just talks about my content strategy.
This one just checks Fireflies. All of
these have a very, very specific thing
that they do. And that's going to get
overwhelming quick unless you have kind
of like your own leadership team up top
that delegates work around. Because you
can see if I click into Klouse, not only
can I talk to Klouse, but he is able to
talk to everyone else. He's able to
delegate work around to all of these
bots. You can see that Claus can send
messages to Dan, Becky, Chandler, Dev,
Eyes, Views, Minor, Motion, Money, Dash,
Cal, Coffee. All of the agents can talk
to each other. And that's when it gets
really cool. As long as you're making
sure you're scaling it up in a way where
the agents don't get confused about
who's doing what and how to talk to each
other and stuff like that. You don't
want to have them duplicating work or
leaving holes in your plans, things like
that. And I know this interface may seem
a little bit intimidating right now, but
trust me, it's not going to be bad at
all. Just to show you some other stuff
that's possible in each agent, you
basically are going to have a name,
which is what you see over here. You'll
have a label, which is optional if you
want to give them like a role, like a
job title. And then you have a
description, and that is actually what
tells other agents what does this agent
do. So, for example, for Klouse, this
description is you are Nate's chief of
staff. Klouse is the only bot that Nate
talks to. Before doing any task, check
whether another Grockbot owns it and
delegate first. Only do the work
yourself if no specialist fits and then
bring the result back here. You can have
notifications turned on for specific
bots. And then also what you can do is
that you can see each bot has their own
computer. Now they they have their own
screens but they do share the same
computer. So if you authenticate into
like school.com or if you log into
something then other bots will be able
to access that too but they have their
own screen. So right here you can see it
was literally in its own CLI
authenticating into GitHub. You can see
that it was looking at my Herk 2 repo.
You can see that it was looking at our
school community and it's logged in as
me as you can see. So, it can help me
take action inside of AIS or AIS Plus
and things like that. You can see it was
also searching for Chicago Cubs food.
I'm not sure what it was doing, but the
point is I can control the browser and
so can Claus and so can the other
agents. You can also see there's
something called routines. This one for
Claus is called a Sunday work log
archive. It runs every Sunday night. And
what this does is it takes everything
that we did this week in ClickUp because
I have every project that gets logged or
created inside of my Grockbot be stored
in ClickUp so I can view it later and
comment on it and stuff like that. It
basically takes anything in here that we
marked as complete for the week and then
it pushes them into a different one
called the archive. So I can actually
see what we've done and make sure that
things on our actual main work log are
staying clean. Now all of the agents can
contribute to this and push things
around, but Klouse is kind of the one I
would say Claus and Dan are both the two
that are in charge of keeping it cleaned
and keeping things like moving forward.
But they could also be like every 5
minutes, every 10 minutes. They could
also be certain other types of triggers
where if I go to here, you can see it
could be like on a Slack message or on a
Teams message. There's not a ton right
now, but I know that they're working on
adding a ton more triggers like off of
emails or calendar events and things
like that as well. So, anyways, just
wanted to give you a super quick
interface tour, uh, a super quick 30,000
foot view of where we're going. And now
what we're going to do is we're going to
actually dive into getting this set up
if you've never opened it up before. All
right, Grockpot, let's do it. So, this
is kind of the dream, right? People are
looking at this one main AI agent that
just controls a swarm of agents. And
this is cool and it's possible, but the
problem with this is that it gets a
little bit confusing because this agent
becomes overwhelmed because it has so
many different agents to pick through
and things as you scale can just get a
little bit messy. So, what we want to
try to set up is more of this sort of
style where we have you that just talks
to a few executives and we'll scale
these up slowly as you realize you need
them. And then all of these executives
are basically aware of, okay, these are
the three agents that I talk to the
most. These are the three agents that I
talk to the most. And these are kind of
more of like your operator agents that
do something very specifically within
the overall vertical. So if this was
more of like your, you know, let's just
say the marketing team, then these are
little marketing operation agents. If
this is the finance team, then these are
like accountants and like just things,
just little agents that do one very
specific task. So that's something that
I'm trying to communicate through is you
don't want to just have one mega agent
that does everything. You want to have a
bunch of specialized agents that do one
thing very very well and then they just
get called on whenever it's time to do
that thing by like their manager
essentially. And what's really cool is
that even though these are operators,
they can still talk to each other. So if
they realize, oh shoot, like in order to
run this weekly report, I actually need
to get data from um this team over here
real quick. And so it'll just reach out
over here, get that data, come back and
keep working. And so that's why things
like having a description for each agent
be very very clear of what this person
actually does. Now, real quick, what I
wanted to talk about is the difference
between something like Hermes or
Grockbot or Codeex or Cloud Code because
if you guys have been using my channel
or using if you guys have been following
my channel for a while, then you know
that I really like to use Claude Code
and Codeex. But I really see these in
two different buckets. I kind of see
these two tools being in the same bucket
and then I kind of see these two tools
being in the same bucket as well. And
what I mean by that is when I'm sitting
down here at my desk and I'm doing sort
of like my my daily knowledge work and
I'm building things, I'm always going to
use cloud code or codecs. You know,
Grockbot is basically being used by the
XAI, the Grock models. And these are
being driven by GBT models, cloud
models. And I think overall I like these
models better for, you know, production
work and building things. Um, obviously
you can switch out the models, but the
point being, these are the harnesses
that I like to use when I'm sitting down
at my desk and driving work and
projects. These are the agents that I
like to use because I can have them on
my phone and because I can have them on
the go and because I just really like
spinning up automations with them. So, I
think of these as like, you know,
sitting down and you're doing work at
your computer. And I think of these as
building automations and agents that you
can talk to while you're at lunch or
when you're on a vacation or when you
want to set up something that just kind
of runs overnight while you're sleeping
or runs in the background based on some
sort of event trigger. So if I wanted to
build my own little team to run like an
Instagram account fully autonomously, I
would probably use a Grockbot. But if I
wanted to build myself some skills and a
production pipeline to generate a bunch
of, you know, Instagram reels or
carousels at scale, I would probably
just build that within something like
this. So anyways, hopefully that paints
a little bit more color here. Don't get
too overwhelmed about that. I will kind
of talk about while we're building out
stuff in Grockbot what I think are good
use cases and what might not be, but
just wanted to call that out in case you
guys were thinking about that. And I
know that there's a lot of AI tools
going around. So I don't want to add
more like overwhelm or confusion to your
head. So we talked about this. What I
want to talk about now is my framework
for how we actually do this effectively.
And I call this an AI operating system.
And I call this my four C's of building
an effective AI operating system. So the
four C's are context, connections,
capabilities, and cadence. I think of
these two as sort of like the
information about this Grock agent or
whatever you're building that makes it
specific to you. And then I think about
these as the things that help the agent
move faster. So context is like giving
it information about you, giving it
information about your business, giving
it information about your goals and
what's important to you and how you
work. I then think of connections as
giving the agent access to the things
that you need to pull data from. So
obviously connecting it to your email,
to your calendar, to your Slack, to
your, you know, your bank accounts if
you want to, connecting it to things so
it can read what's going on in real time
in your business besides just giving it
like static data, but also allowing it
to take action. So creating drafts if
you want, you know, creating ClickUp
tasks if you want, doing all of those
sorts of things, creating Google Docs,
you know, generating slides, generating
assets. That's actually a big part of
the power is connecting it to different
sources. But if you don't give it the
context first, it's not going to
understand what do I do with these
connections? Why are these important?
And how do I actually make deliverables
for you that are good and like valuable
for your business? And then we talk
about capabilities. This is basically
combining the previous two things. So
now we're going to give it capabilities,
which a lot of times we're going to be
calling skills, um, to actually give it
instructions on how to do something
well. So, if you want it to be able to
create you good proposals, you need to
give it the context to make those
proposals and the connections to
actually do that in like a Google doc or
something. If you want it to be able to
scrape LinkedIn and help you write
LinkedIn posts, you have to give it all
of this context and connections to do
so. So, capabilities is where you really
start to give it basically like more
tools and more skills. And then from
there, we have cadence and those are the
routines I talked about. These are
building the automations that help this
thing scale besides the fact of you just
like saying, "Hey, can you do this? Can
you do this?" making this thing more
autonomous and intelligent so it knows,
oh boom, this happened in Nate's
business. I need to do this or hey, this
agent reached out to me to do this. I
better check in here and I better do
this so that when Nate wakes up, he's
good to go. And once you kind of like
keep having this loop of creating more
of all four of these four C's, then you
get in a really cool spot with your
crockbots. Okay, so the rough agenda of
today was this. We kind of already took
a little bit of a tour and as we get set
up, I'm still going to be pointing
things out and calling things out and
then we're going to go through those
four C's. I'm going to show you what it
looks like to start adding context. I'm
going to show you what it looks like to
start adding connections and
capabilities and cadence. And then we're
going to pretty much end off once we've
got a bunch of different agents running.
And I'm just going to go over some hacks
and some things that I like to do that
really help you get more out of building
your Grock bots. So, that's kind of the
rough agenda of today. There's going to
be timestamps down below if you want to
kind of skip around a little bit or save
parts and come back to them later, but
let's just go ahead and get set up with
a brand new Grockbot. Okay, so what you
want to do is go to Google and just type
Grockbot and it's going to be probably
the first link. AI teammates that
finished the work. You're going to click
here. This is the page that I showed you
guys earlier. And what you're going to
do is just go ahead and download this
for your operating system. And then also
go ahead and install this on the iOS app
if you want to be able to use them
together. I'll show that off later in a
bit. But when you're here, you're going
to go to pricing. And basically, you can
get access to Grockbot for just 30 bucks
a month. So it used to be when it first
came out, it was just the 200 bucks a
month, but now it's 30 bucks a month.
So, you're just going to go ahead and
upgrade your plan to Super Grock. And
then whatever email you did that with,
that's the one you're going to sign in
with when you open up the desktop app.
So, I'm just going to go ahead and
upgrade to Super Grock right now. And
I'm going to create a new account for
the 30 bucks a month plan. So, you can
see how far does 30 bucks a month
actually get you on your, you know,
usage. So, I'm going to go ahead and
sign up for this. Okay. So, I just
signed up for the 30 bucks a month
subscription. We are now good to go
inside of this account and I've
downloaded the app. So, what I'm going
to do is go back into the app. I'm going
to come in here and I'm going to log out
and then we're going to log back into
this fresh account. So, sign in and then
sign in with the email that you just
used obviously to create that account.
I'm authorizing Grockbot to read my
profile, read my email address, do
things like that, and then we're going
to go ahead and continue through the
data sharing so that we now get into
Grockbot. And I'm going to click sign
in. And then we should be able to go
right back into our desktop app and get
set up. So, it's setting up Grockbot's
computer. And this is all basically
going on in Gro's cloud. Meaning it
automatically is going to sync to your
phone. You can turn off your computer,
you can close out of the desktop app,
and it's still going to be able to work.
So that's why I like it so much is
because with other things like Hermes or
setting up like Cloud Code on a VPS and
all this stuff to have that like always
on feel, even something like OpenClaw,
it's not that hard, but it did feel a
bit more technical because you kind of
had to set up like a VPS or you had to
have a manage app. But this is basically
all taken care of for you right away. So
meet Grockbot. We're going to go ahead
and click next. It says that Grockbot
has its own computer and works just like
you. Cool. Give each bot a job. So, this
is what I talked about. You don't want
to build one mega agent. You want to
have each agent doing something very,
very specific for your business that
provides value. Um, what do you use
every day? So, if you want to click
through here and connect some stuff,
feel free. I definitely use Google
Workspace. Definitely want to connect
something like, you know, GitHub,
LinkedIn, ClickUp. You can connect
whatever you need to. But hey, if you
forget about it here and you go ahead
and click next, don't worry because you
can connect things easily anytime. And
I'll show you guys of that, of course.
But now we have to create our first bot.
So this one, I want you to just think of
this one as your personal assistant,
your executive assistant, the one that
you're going to talk to the most. So
give it whatever kind of name you want.
For now, I'm honestly just going to call
this one friend because he's going to be
my best friend. And we're going to go
ahead and just make this one a blue
square. So let's get started with
friend. It's going to spin up that first
agent. And what's going to happen is
before I even say anything, it's going
to start talking to us. It's going to
say, "Hey, my name's friend. What can I
help you with?" Like, "What's important
to you? What is my job?" That's what
it's going to start doing at first. And
this is where we really start to get
into that first C of the context. We're
going to start giving this thing our
information for who we are. Hey Nate,
good to meet you. What do you actually
want me in your day for? As you can see,
so what I'm going to do is I'm just
going to start giving it some
information. Hey friend, my name is
Nate. I am not technical at all. I don't
really have a ton of experience with
setting up Grockbots and things like
that. So, when you're explaining things
to me and when we're setting things up,
I just need you to explain it to me
concise and an easy way. But, I run a
home services company. It's called
Summit Home Services and I want you to
help me because I have a small team, but
I want to be able to do more and scale
my revenue. And so, just start off with
something very similar like that or very
simple like that. Messed up Grockbots
here, but friend should be just fine.
Now, while this is responding, you can
see if I go in here and I go to my
settings, we have a name. It doesn't yet
have a label, but you can see that based
on the thing that I filled out earlier,
it says the user works with Workspace,
GitHub, LinkedIn, ClickUp everyday.
Start with these tools when suggesting
connectors or taking on work. This is
where we could change the description
and add a label. Anyways, now it says
you're running Summit with a small team
and you want to grow without drowning.
That's a thing that I can actually help
with. Where's the pinch right now? Now,
here's what I'm going to do. I'm just
going to say, give me one second. I'm
just going to give you a document that
has a bunch of information about my
business already. And then we can talk
more about like bottlenecks and stuff
like that. And so why I'm doing this is
because I want to show you the first
connector. And if you already have
information like this in your business,
which a lot of you guys probably do,
give it to Grockbot. So this is just
basically an internal operations and
knowledge base. You can see we have our
company snapshot. We can have hours of
operations, services we offer, pricing.
And so this is just going to be easier
than me explaining to Grockbot
everything about my business. So, what
I'm going to do is I'm just going to go
ahead and copy this link. I'm going to
go back into Grockbot and I'm just going
to give it this link and say, "Hey, go
ahead and read this doc and just, you
know, save this to your actual memory so
that you know this about me and my
business." And what's going to happen
here is this thing currently has no arms
at all. This is basically just an LLM
that we can talk to. So, it's going to
try to read this and it's going to
realize, wait a minute, I can't. And
then I'm going to show you how we
actually connect it to something like
Google Workspace so that it can actually
read through this type of stuff. and
then we'll continue going on about
figuring out other agents to make and
things like that. The first thing it
says is that the link is locked because
if you can see here, this basically
says, hey, you know, only people with
the link can access to it. So, it should
be able to open it up and it's going to
try to do this in its actual computer.
So, if we go in here, you can see that
it's going to paste in that link and
it's going to go to that account, but
now it's going to try to sign in and
it's not going to be able to access that
doc. So, there's going to be a much
easier way to actually give it access to
Google Docs, Gmail, Calendar, all that.
So it comes back and it says, "Hey, the
easiest fix is to come back and connect
Google Drive so I can read it." So sign
in with the same Google account that has
the doc and then tell me. So I'm just
going to click on this connector and it
says add from plugins. So I click on
that and all I have to do is click on
add. And then what makes it super easy
here is that all we have to do is
authenticate. And one quick tip before
you start authenticating a bunch of
stuff is to label them because if you
want to authenticate into a bunch of
different Google accounts, you want to
be able to know which one's which. So,
I'm just going to come in here and I'm
just going to call this one Nate Herk8
because that's the one that I'm
authenticating. And then it changes the
name. And then I click authenticate. And
it just pulls up the Google window for
you to actually sign in. So there's not
a bunch of having to deal with all these
little API keys and technical things.
You're just signing in like you would on
your own computer. So I'm going to go
ahead and sign into my account here. I'm
going to select what Grock can access.
So right here it says, do you want to
let it see and download or do you want
to let it see, edit, create, and delete?
And I'm fine with both of those. If you
don't feel comfortable with letting it
edit and delete, then maybe you want to
be careful about like what you give it
access to. But in this case, I wanted it
to do all that. So now I have
authenticated my Google Drive and I will
say go ahead and try again now that that
is authenticated. And now friend is
going to go ahead and keep working
pulling up the doc. It's going to read
it and then hopefully what we're looking
for is that it's actually saving this to
memory so that it knows later if we are
talking about other things about our
business, it actually can answer that
kind of stuff. And you can see it's
actually telling you what it's doing.
It's connecting to our Google Drive, the
Nate Herk8, and then it's going to kind
of, you know, reason and think and take
action and come back to us. And that is
kind of called an agentic loop within
these agent harnesses. You can see now
it's working. So, it has this loop of it
looks at something, it thinks, takes
action, looks, thinks, takes action, and
that's how it decides to stop or decides
to respond to you, things like that. So,
anyways, it saved it. Summit is HVAC in
the Twin Cities, small team. Fix it, not
upsell. The money leak is slow email
replies and busy season. That's the job
you actually want me for. And if you
want me on that, then tap Gmail and tell
me and I'll look at the inbox. Okay, so
here's where I want to pause a little
bit. We want to get set up with some
email stuff, right? I put a bunch of
fake emails inside of this account. This
was our receipt from Groai. But anyways,
I put a bunch of emails in here about
our business, right? Fake emails about
from customers, you know, like, hey,
this charge or hey, I want an
appointment. all this kind of stuff and
it's hard for me to manage that. But
what we want to do is we might want to
have one individual agent that's job is
just to help us like triage emails or
respond to them and create drafts and
things like that. So what I'm going to
do is I think you're right. I think it
would be good for me to connect you to
Gmail so you can help me out with like
responding and triaging. But because I'm
treating you as like my chief of staff,
I think that we should create a separate
agent and its job is basically only
helping out with these emails. And while
that's happening, I'm just going to go
into my friend, my settings, and I'm
just going to call this one chief of
staff. And what I'm going to do is also
just going to go ahead and pin this
agent because this is the one I want to
talk to the most. I don't want to get
overwhelmed with all of these different
agents that it is going to create for
us. Now, look at this. It actually said,
I'll make an inbox agent whose only job
is to summit emails, and I'll get the
Gmail hooked up for it. So now, right
from here, it messaged inbox. We can
click on this message and see what it
said. This is the message from friend to
inbox agent and it says, "Hey, Nate
created you as the dedicated email
agent. Here's information about the
business. Here's information about the
pricing. Here's how you triage. And
here's what you do." It also gave us the
source of truth, which is the actual
Google Drive. And then it said, "Okay,
cool. Connecting Nate to Gmail now." And
then if I actually click into inbox
agent, it says, "Hey, I got the brief
from friend. I'm going to save this and
I won't do anything until you tell me
to." So that's already a demonstration
of how these agents start to work
together. Anyways, let's go ahead and
authorize our um Gmail now. And it's the
exact same process as we did earlier for
connecting our accounts. We click
authorize. We click the email we want to
connect to. We allow these different
permissions. And then we hit continue.
And now when we go back into Grockbot,
that should basically be added. Now,
what I want to do real quick is give
that a label, right? We talked about
that earlier. All you have to do is
you're going to go to plugins. You're
going to see that we have two installed.
And right here we have Google Drive. We
have Gmail. I'd click into this one. And
I would just change the name right here
by calling this Nate Herk 88. Making
sure that name has been changed. And
while you're in the plug-in section, you
can see how many other ones there are.
There's calendar, granola, AWS agents,
there's plane, there's ampify, there's
so many different things in here. And
you basically can search for them, or
you can click on these different
categories. And so I'll talk more about
these other plugins later, but that's
basically how you start building in the
connections like we talked about to give
your Grockbots access to actually do
things. So that's where it is. It's
called plugins. Anyways, let's see
what's going on here. So, friend has a
message for us. It says, "Playbook is
saved. Gmail's connected. Want me to
start triaging the inbox? I'll pull
emergencies and warm leads first, and I
still won't send anything until you say
so." So, it's okay for us right now when
we're setting up inbox, when we're
setting up these sort of automations and
things that we want it to do, it's okay
to talk to inbox. The point I was trying
to make is at some point you just want
to make sure that if you need to
delegate workaround or if you need for
um you know automations to go through,
you should make sure that friend
understands that it knows where other
agents live and what they're good at.
And the way you do that is by having um
that knowledge set up. So if I go to
inbox and I click on the settings, you
can see that it says here already your
only job is to summit house services
customer email. This is what you do and
friend can read this to make sure it
knows what inbox should be doing. I'm
also going to give this one a quick
label, which is basically our um email
agent. Cool. Now, what I'm going to do
is I'm inside of inbox already. So,
we're going to just help him get set up
with the what we want to do in the
inbox. So, the inbox is pretty messy. I
think that there's probably a few
different tasks and automations that
we're going to set up for you. But
first, what I want you to do is just
read the emails that we have in there
and make some suggestions to me. I'm
basically the only person at the company
that responds to company emails. So,
help me figure out what would be the
highest value. We probably need to have
them labeled. we probably need different
automations set up. What do you think
makes sense to help me run this company
more efficiently? And it's going to go
through that agentic loop of
understanding our message, looking
inside the the inbox, reading things,
and then kind of giving us some
recommendations. All right, so inbox
came back with quite a bit of
information here. I actually don't
really know if I like the name inbox,
but we'll keep it for now because it's
pretty clear. But one of my favorite
quotes that I really want you guys to
internalize is that you can outsource
the thinking, but you cannot outsource
the understanding. And what I mean by
that in this context is that you can see
I said, "Hey, look at my inbox and help
me figure out what makes the most
sense." Now, what that means is inbox
went out, read everything, and now it's
giving me some recommendations. But that
doesn't mean I just blindly say, "Yeah,
do all of that." Because one of the big
mistakes I see with people getting set
up with agents and automations is they
just build so much right away and then
they lose track of what's actually going
on and then it starts to just not even
provide value because what they were
building might not have actually solved
the problem. And for this example
scenario, we know that managing the
inbox is an actual bottleneck in the
business and it is a problem we want to
solve, but we want to solve it, right?
So, anyways, got that out of the way.
Now, let me look at what this response
is. So, it read through the whole inbox.
Two of these need you today. So, Marcus
has no heat. You know, he's got a
newborn. Here's his phone number. Hannah
has a water heater leaking in the
basement. Those have both been unread
for a couple hours this morning. The
inbox also has 5200 emails. It's unread.
So, I'm just going to ignore that
because it's just this is just an old
email. Um, so the highest value isn't
cleaning those old emails, but it's
making sure that the next emergency
never sits and that you only see the
mail that needs you. I agree. So, it
wants to create six labels on customer
emails. Emergency, needs you, quote,
schedule, billing, and warranty. Vendors
and SEO pitches get ignored. Skip the
old labels already in there, which I
made for different demos. Anyways, three
new habits that it wants to create. So,
it wants to have a routine that watches
new mail and basically just like pings
you if there's anything really immediate
like emergencies or refunds and angry
customers. Everything else waits for a
short weekday morning list. And then
what it wants to do is draft the easy
replies. So, things that it can answer
based on the documentation I gave it. A
lot of this is super easy kind of just
like customer support FAQ answers that
the bot could use to answer with. And
then it also said the rest of the 30 is
quotes, reschedules, warranties, and a
tech application. Those can wait behind
the two emergency and the money fights.
So where should it start? So in this
case, I think that all of these
recommendations are good. I want it to
draft emails for me. I want it to ping
me with important things and I want
everything to be labeled as well. So,
I'm just going to say do all of it
because one decision that we might have
to make in the future. Probably not yet
because I think that at the moment inbox
can handle all of this. But let's say we
were getting a super high volume of um
refund sort of requests. Maybe at some
point we would want to have inbox agent
triage all of those to an agent that
specifically deals with refund requests
and we can train that agent really well
on here's what you do in X case, here's
what you do in Y case. And then maybe we
even give that refund agent the ability
once we really trust it to actually
process the refund. So I'm not trying to
overwhelm. I'm just saying like thinking
multiple steps ahead. That's where we
could go at some point is each agent
takes care of one of those labels. And
so that's why I think it's important to
have like this hierarchy where we mainly
have to communicate to a few and they
can delegate work to a bunch of agents
below them. So you can see it's setting
up those six labels now and then it's
going to draft the two emergency replies
and turn on a watch. Still not going to
send anything. We're keeping everything
as drafts for now, which I think is
still a good way to start. And then when
we fully trust it, we can maybe start to
scale up those capabilities. So, first
thing I want to call out is it created a
routine. It created a routine called
inbox emergency watch. It says you are
inbox. You are Summit House Services
customer email agent. You're going to
check the connected Gmail account. And
also, I gave it a label just in case
later we add on a bunch of different
email accounts for new inbound customer
mail since the last run. You're going to
look up the Gmail tools. You're going to
blah blah blah. You're never going to
send. You're just going to create
drafts. Here's what you do on each run.
So, this is basically if you've ever
created some sort of SOP for a specific
process in your business that you're
going to give to a human. You're
basically just onboarding and training
how a human would do it, but you're just
telling an agent how to do it. It's just
very specific step-by-step instructions
as you can see. And what you see here is
that it says when to run every 30
minutes. So, every single 30 minutes,
every day of the month between 12 a.m.
and 11 p.m., so pretty much the entire
day, this is going to check. And if
there's no emails that fit into this
specific category, then it's just going
to do nothing. And it might even say,
"Hey, I just did a check. No actions."
But if there is something urgent, then
it will go ahead and actually run that.
But now, let's take a look at what it
said. It created the routine, but then
it created drafts for these two. So, if
I actually go into my inbox, you can see
that we still have all of these emails,
which are right here. But if I go to
drafts, we have two more right now. And
the agent left these as unread so that
we can still see them. It also, as you
see, it just tagged them. And if I go
back to my inbox, you can see all of
these are now labeled with quote,
emergency, schedule, needs you. This one
even has two billing and needs you,
needs you, and quote, emergency. And so,
anyways, what we did is inside of our
drafts, it only took in the two that
were labeled as emergencies, and it went
ahead and created drafts for me. So,
let's click into one of them, right?
This one said urgent, no water, or
sorry, no heat. The house is freezing.
It says, you know, please help. We woke
up this morning. I'll pay the fee.
Here's my number. And then the response
is, "Hey Marcus, sorry you're dealing
with this, especially with a newborn in
the house. This is an emergency. We'll
treat that right away. Someone from our
team will call you shortly at blah blah
blah. Sunday emergency visits have $150
emergency fee on top of the diagnostic.
Please reply with the service address so
we can get a tech out to you." Cool. So,
good response, right? Um I also can see
in this one we have a response as well
that highlights what um Hannah said at
this point. Now, one thing that you
might want to think of is if you have
some sort of way that you as a business
like to communicate or if you have some
sort of special sign off that you like
or you know, like I said, just a way
that you like to communicate. That's
where you could come back into Grockbot
and say, "Hey, by the way, you should
always be responding like this. Here is
basically our tone of voice so that
everything you draft is already kind of
like on brand." But anyways, what I'm
going to do is I'm just going to go
ahead and say, "Yeah, go ahead and send
both because we went in there and we
approved them and now it's going to
shoot those off." You can also see that
it created those labels which was really
good. And what I want you guys to notice
is that that happened super quick and it
also wasn't hard at all. We connected
Gmail. We gave it pretty simple
instructions on what to do and then it
just went ahead and took action. And now
we get into this thing called the
feedback loop which I actually call this
um riding the bike or the bike method.
So what I mean by that is when you first
start building agents or you first start
building capabilities, you have to think
about it like you're teaching a kid to
ride a bike. Meaning, we can't just
expect that everything's perfect and
that it's going to work on the first try
perfectly. These labels look pretty
good, but if we really looked into them,
we'd probably notice a few things that
we don't like. And that's the whole idea
of when you use AI for something,
obviously, the end goal and the the
motivation is that it's turning out to
something that's 100% done, 100%
accurate. But more realistically, what
happens is as you start building, it
gets you like maybe this much of the way
there. And then you have to say, "Hey,
this is what you did good. this is what
you did bad. Try again. And then you get
here and you keep giving it feedback
over time until you get to the point
where you're like this much confident,
right? And so why I call that the bike
method is because you would never just
put your kid on the bike and then say,
"Hey, just just pedal. Just pedal. Stay
balanced. You'll be good because they're
going to fall and it's going to be bad."
What you do is you put them on the bike,
you hold the handlebar, you have one
hand on their back, and you're watching
them and guiding them. And then slowly
over time, you build more trust and you
give them feedback. You know, hey,
you're leaning too far to the right. You
have to keep your weight in the middle.
try that and let's try again. And then
slowly you start to take your hands off
and you're still walking next to the the
kid and then you know you you put the
training wheels on and you're not
touching at all. But even when you feel
really confident about their ability,
you're probably not going to say, "Hey
kid, go ride your bike." And then you're
going to go inside and take a nap.
You're still going to like sit in the
driveway and watch. You're still going
to like be in the kitchen and just be
near in case you hear them crying or
whatever it is. The point I'm trying to
make here is this stuff is amazing and
it makes you so much more capable, but
it's not magic. And people that treat it
like magic, and that's why I said
earlier, people that come in here, they
build 15 agents on day one, they don't
test it. They just say, "Okay, cool. Now
I have an agent swarm." Those are the
people that run into trouble when
clients get messages that shouldn't have
gone out. And the agents start inter,
you know, uh, conflicting with each
other and things die in the middle of
the night. That's where you get into
these scary situations. Awesome. So now
those replies have been sent. Let's talk
about some capabilities here. This was
obviously a capability and cadence
because it already created this
automation for us. And so really what
that would look like is I would come
into here and I would like maybe grab
five of these emails and say, "Okay, so
for this email, this actually should
have been labeled as quote for this X,
Y, and Z reason. And this re this email
should have been labeled as, you know,
needs you and schedule for this X, Y,
and Z reason." And every time it does
something and you give it that feedback
loop, it literally will say, "Okay,
cool. I've updated the instructions, so
next time I can do this better." And you
have to keep doing that feedback loop.
And that's where you usually start to
turn something into a formal skill. So,
let's just go ahead and build a skill.
Hey, inbox, that looks good. What I want
you to do now is we're going to build a
skill. And I want the skill to be weekly
email report. And the deliverable that
I'm looking for out of this skill is a
Google sheet. So, what I want you to do
is set up a new routine on Fridays at
5:00 p.m. So, the end of the week. And
when you run this routine, I want you to
invoke this skill that we're building.
And what this does is it looks at all of
the emails that you labeled in the past
week. So, Monday through Friday. And
then what I want you to do is generate
me a one-page Google sheet with
analytics on um how many requests were
in each of the labels. Maybe look at
things like average response time and
just give me the analytics on like the
types of requests we're getting because
this data is going to help us build more
automations in the future. You know,
kind of tackling things that are the
highest priority. So if you have any
questions about that process, ask me.
But otherwise, let's go ahead and start
building out the skill and, you know,
give me an example deliverable.
And so one of the things I did there is
pretty key. I obviously told it what I
wanted in the skill. I told it, you
know, what the deliverable is, but I
always like to say, you know, like ask
me questions about this until you
understand. Because if you don't give it
a specific enough definition of done,
then it's going to give you something
that's really bad. And if you just said,
hey, you know, ask me questions until
you understand what I'm looking for and
understand what you should be doing,
then it will basically keep interviewing
you until it has a lot better
understanding. So this is a pretty
simple request. It's not too difficult
and so it probably doesn't have a lot of
questions for us. But a lot of times
when you're planning out like a new
automation or you're planning out a new
project, it will ask you a lot of
questions to make sure you guys are on
the same page. And also what you'll
notice is when I said I want you to
build this new routine, invoke the
skill. So skills are basically just
instructions. Skills are, you know, if
you it's it's a recipe. So let's say you
want to build um not build, you want to
make some chocolate chip pancakes. And
I'm just going to do a real quick
terrible drawing of a person. Um, let's
just say they're looking at some sort of
recipe. So, this is the the chocolate
chip pancakes recipe. Let's say you read
the recipe and now you're making these
chocolate chip pancakes that are just,
you know, absolutely incredible. They're
so delicious. Now, what happens if you
want to make more the next week? You
probably want to reuse that same recipe
because it turned out so well. Or what
if these turned out really bad? you
would probably update the recipe and
say, "Okay, you know, I think that I
cooked these each for too long on each
side, so next time I'm going to do a
minute less on each side." And so this
is basically the IP you're building here
is the instructions. Oops. The
instructions of this recipe is what
you're building. So that every time your
agent says, "Okay, I need chocolate chip
pancakes. All I have to do is I just
have to go over here and read the
chocolate chip pancake skill or recipe."
And then you're going to basically just
turn into a resource library where you
have a skill for every single process
and every single automation in your
business. And then all that you need to
do is make sure that your agents, just
pretend this is like the Grockbot logo
or something. Every single one of your
agents is aware of all of these skills
so that all it has to do when it
understands, okay, I have this new
instruction. I have this new goal that I
need to work towards. All I have to do
is find the right skill, read it, and
then take action. So when I say skill,
that's basically what I mean. So
switching back into Grockbot, you can
see that we have a new routine. So now
inbox already has two cadence set up. It
has the every 30 minutes inbox watch and
it has the every Friday at 5 email
report. It also said here's a sample. So
if I click on the weekly email report, I
go into here and I get a Google sheet.
And how do I have this Google sheet?
Well, because if you remember in our
plugins, we already connected Google
Drive which already had Drive, Docs,
Sheets, probably Slides as well. So we
already have this deliverable that I
could once again open this up on my
phone too. But now you can see we have
the week, we have a note, we have the
total of emails, we have how many are
still waiting, we have average time to
response, we have all of these stats, we
have a breakdown. Now let's say we
actually want to have this be visual and
this is really ugly. Well, we come back
into Gro and say, "Hey, I think that
this is good as far as the data, but I
need you to make two changes. What I
need you to do is um add some color in
here." So add like formal headers and,
you know, columns and bold text and use
colors. our brand guidelines as far as
colors, we really like to use green is
like our primary color. So add some
green in there. And then also I want you
to add a chart. I wish that you had like
a pie chart or maybe even a bar chart as
well on the actual breakdown by label
just so we have a better way to
visualize this data. So what I want you
to do is make the changes to that Google
sheet and then update the skill so that
next time you run this on Friday, we
already have these changes baked in.
Cool. So, I'm going to shoot that off.
And what I'm going to show you while
this is running is what this skill
actually looks like. If I open this
skill, it pops up right here. It has a
name. It has a description. So, use this
when producing a weekly labeled email
analytics report, blah blah blah. And
then it also has instructions. So, this
is basically very similar to the
instructions that we read earlier in the
routines, just step-by-step instructions
of what to do. You know, here is the
input, here's what you're building, here
are the steps, here's what you should be
doing. And what's going to happen is
this is what inbox is going to update.
So it's going to come back in here later
and say, "Oh, you also need to have like
a pie chart and a bar chart." And also
make sure that the columns are always
colored in this way. So this is
basically the living recipe that it will
continue to update over time. And if you
want to be able to access it rather than
just like clicking on it right here, you
can go to your plugins, you go to
installed, and then you actually just
see them right here as private plugins.
That's kind of what they're calling them
here. But they're very much skills. And
the cool thing is if you have skills
from cloud code or codeex, you can bring
them in here and you can also invoke
them with slash commands as you see very
similar to the way you do in cloud cod
or codex. Right here you can see that we
have this weekly email report skill
which is the one that we just built
together. Cool. So while this is
actually building out, let me just talk
about the actual um way that you're
paying for this. So if you guys
remember, I'm on the 30 bucks a month
plan. And if I go to my name, you can
see that we have something right here
called our usage. And this resets in 7
days. Right now we're 6% of the way
through out of 100%. And this is where
if we wanted to change our limit, we
could come in here and we could upgrade
to 100 bucks a month or we could upgrade
to um you know 200 bucks a month or
whatever it actually is. But this is
where we can see our usage. And so I'll
keep checking in on this so you can see
out of everything that we're doing today
together how long this will probably
last you. Once again, while it runs
these routines while you're sleeping or
when you're on your phone, all of that
contributes to your email and your usage
right here. Now, real quick, while this
is running, I wanted to show you guys on
my phone. You can see it's pulled up
right over here. This is our account. I
can go into inbox, and you can see that
it's completely synced right here. If I
said awesome, let me take a look. As
soon as I send that, that'll also send
on my computer. So, all of this is
completely synced. I can click into the
skill and look at that on my phone. I
can go to the actual Google sheet if I
want to over here, although I'm in a
different account, so I'd have to
switch. But the point being, all of this
is now accessible on my phone as well,
and it stays perfectly synced. I could
come into here. I could message this
agent as well. So, really, that's all it
is. It's it syncs in real time
instantly. And now you have this in your
phone in your pocket as well. Okay. So,
I'm going to go ahead and click into the
sheet on my actual desktop here. Well,
what happened? We don't yet see any
changes. I even do a refresh. Let's see.
Did it say I'm checking whether the
green headers and charts have actually
landed yet? The numbers are in the
cheat. The color and charts didn't stick
yet, so I'm putting those in now. Okay.
I'm not exactly sure what happened, but
what's good is I didn't have to give it
feedback. It basically proved to me that
it verified itself. It opened it up. It
realized, oh, you know, I didn't
actually fix anything. So, let me go
ahead and fix that now. Aha.
Interesting. Okay. So, it said the sheet
is still plain. To add the green headers
and charts, I need you to sign into
Google on my computer once. So, what we
need to do now is we're going to take
over the computer. This is going to pop
up this interface. We just need to sign
in with our account and then it will be
able to use this computer to do
formatting and stuff and it will save
this login across the computer that all
your other Grock bots can use. So at
this point I'm just going to go ahead
and sign into that account real quick.
You can see like I said I'm able to
drive this as well as Grockbot being
able to drive this and then we'll go
ahead and get signed in. Okay, so now
I've signed in. You can see that we're
looking at the weekly report. So I'm
just going to go ahead and click I'm
done. And now Inbox should be able to
get in there and fix that. And you can
actually see right here if I open this
up, it's mouse is going around and
highlighting things and taking action,
you know, right here. If I actually I'll
go into the the one in the web. This is
me, but this is actually Grockpot right
here taking action using the browser.
And so there is this function in here
called teach a task, which basically
means that I could record myself in this
browser doing something. So, I could
record myself formatting this with
different fonts and different colors and
highlighting and then I could stop
recording and then that would teach
Grockbot the skill and then it would
watch the recording and it would
understand what do I click and where and
how do I do it. So, that's something we
could do. I honestly don't like this
function. Like I don't use it very much.
I'd rather just instruct it with my
natural language. But it is a nice
built-in feature that's pretty helpful,
especially if you do have a couple tasks
that you do have to do by opening up a
browser and clicking into different
places and maybe downloading reports and
things like that. It's a nice feature to
know about, but I will be honest, I just
don't use it very much. Awesome. So,
that took about 7 minutes and now you
can see that it has created those
elements. It also was taking screenshots
to prove to me that they are built and
that the colors work and that everything
looks good. So, if I open up that actual
doc, you can see we now have these green
colors. We have everything organized
more like an actual table. It's a lot
more readable. It's a lot easier to
digest. And now we also have this pie
chart, emails by label. And then we also
have replied versus waiting. So there's
a lot of emails waiting right here. We
have some work to do. But now next
Friday at the end of the week, we're
going to get a report that looks just
like this. And if there's anything that
we want to add to it, any tweaks, any
changes, all we have to do is come back
into inbox and say, "Hey, make these
changes. Update the skill for me." And I
did want to double click on this whole
verification loop idea. It's really
important that you are thinking about
these agents as humans. And what I mean
by that is when a human gives you work,
you are typically going to review it
before you like, you know, consider it
done. At least if you're managing that
human. And however you normally verify
that the work is done and that it meets
sort of like the definition of good,
then that's when you would either accept
it or you would give feedback. And the
idea I'm trying to make here is most of
the time agents can verify their own
work before they give it to you. So
rather than them giving you V1, why
don't you have them give you V4 or V7
that they've already basically said,
"Hey, before I give this to Nate, let me
review it. If I notice any changes, I'll
have to fix it and then I'll review it
again." And so every single thing that I
delegate to my agents, I always have a
verification process in there. If
they're making me a video, I tell them
to screenshot all the frames and make
sure everything looks good. If I'm
having them create me a research report,
I'm telling them to double check and
triple check every single credible
source to make sure that there's no
conflicting information and to make sure
that the sources are like all relevant
within 3 months or something. Whatever
you would do as a human to verify the
work and consider it good, just tell
your agents to do that first. And it
doesn't come back perfect like I said
earlier, but now the first thing they're
handing you is a lot closer to done than
what they would have initially handed
you because they would have just kind of
quit too early to be honest. So that's
what we got. Now, what I want to talk
about is one of the things that just
happened. So, when we sent off this um
email, if I go to my sent and we go to
um this one, we basically said, "Hey,
someone from our team will call you
shortly." Now, here's the thing. No one
actually did that unless I as the
founder of this business am going to
reach out to my team and say, "Hey, you
need to follow up with this person." So,
why don't we have a system where we have
a Grockbot that can delegate the work
out? So, what I'm going to do now is I'm
going to go back to friend because
friend is my chief of staff. Whenever
I'm confused about where to talk or who
to help spin up things, I'm just going
to go back to friend. So, I just worked
with inbox a little bit to set up a few
automations around triaging and managing
the inbox, drafting replies, things like
that. Now, what just happened was friend
or sorry, friend, not friend, inbox
helped me draft two emails and I sent
them out to two customers that said,
"Hey, we'll have a team member follow up
with you." Now, what I'm thinking is we
probably need to have an automation
where when inbox delegates work out like
that, we need to have someone actually
follow up. So, what I'm thinking we
should do is we use ClickUp for our task
management. What I want you to help me
figure out is how do we actually take
the emails that inbox is looking at and
create tasks in ClickUp so that we know
that this work is actually getting
assigned to people automatically. So,
right now, this is just kind of the
brainstorming phase. help me figure out
what agents we should spin up and then
let's actually go ahead and build these
automations. And so what I'm probably
going to suggest we do is similar to
what I did with my other Grock bots is
have some sort of list in here where we
can track tasks and assign people work.
Now obviously I'm not going to be
assigning anyone work because Summit is
a fake home services company. But if
everyone in your company lives in
ClickUp, then you could have your
Grockbot actually creating these tasks,
assigning them to people, giving them a
due date, and saying, "Hey, this is the
email that just came in. I'm I'm
assigning this one to you." So let's see
what friend says. Don't add a pile of
agents. Inbox keeps the email and we add
one new teammate called tasks whose only
job is to use ClickUp. So when inbox
tells a customer someone will follow up.
It will ping tasks. Tasks moves the
ClickUp card with the name, phone, what
they need, and how soon. That's the
whole loop. So I want to get to this,
but I want to be thoughtful about the
way we do this inside of ClickUp. So
what I want to do first is let's connect
ClickUp. And I like this idea of having
an agent called tasks. Although I don't
want to call them tasks. Let's just call
him Fred. And what I want to do is I
want to have an overall list inside of
my ClickUp. There's a space called
internal automations. And I want you to
create a list in there for all of the
Summit Home Services Grockbot work. All
of the projects and everything that
you're working on and everything that
other agents are working on. We need to
have everything being logged in here.
But yes, then we will have Fred, this
new agent, um, take a request from inbox
and then delegate it to the correct team
member inside of ClickUp. So that was
basically me taking the suggestion from
friend. We now have Fred. And honestly,
those two names are kind of similar, so
maybe I should change that up. But I
just added a little bit more color to it
to make it more specific to how I
actually want to work. So you can see
that friend messaged Fred and inbox, and
it's probably saying, "Hey, this is the
new teammate. inbox when you're, you
know, delegating workout, you should be
messaging Fred. But anyways, what I have
to do now is authorize ClickUp. So, I'm
just going to click authorize. It's
going to take me to my Google ClickUp.
And all I have to do is connect the
account. So, I went ahead and connected
the workspace. Go back into Grockbot.
That has been added. And now, what I
want to do once again is just make sure
I go in here to my plugins and actually
name that because you might have more
than one click ClickUp account and
that's totally fine. And this one is
actually just my Nate Herk main. So, I'm
just going to call it Nate Herk main.
Make sure I'm keeping myself organized
here. And now let's see what's going on.
So ClickUp is connected. I'm making that
list inside of internal automations. So
you can see it doesn't yet currently
exist. We just have list Grockbot
worklog and Grockbot worklog archive. So
we're looking for one that's maybe
labeled like summit archive or something
or summit log. And now we see that Fred
and inbox are starting to talk. They
were communicating with friend and
they're getting caught up to speed on
this whole uh process. Now let's say I'm
doing a lot of different work with
friend. What I can do is if we're
talking about lots of different things,
you can actually reply to a specific
action or a specific item in a new
conversation. So if I shot this off, it
would open up a different section where
I could, you know, have two different
conversations with friends. So I can
basically have like two different work
streams to keep things more separate. So
it created a list called Summit Home
Services Grockbot. I'm going to go into
the ClickUp and see if it's there.
Perfect. It's right here. It's called
Summit Home Services Grockbot. You can
see that we have call Hannah Whitmore
and we see call Marcus Duller. It said
that I signed both to you. This ClickUp
is your space and you're the only person
blah blah blah. And then it messaged
Fred and inbox once again. So, let's
just see what it sent over to Fred. It
basically said, "Hey, Nate created you
as Fred. Here's what you should be
doing." Fred said, "Okay, I got it. I'm
going to cue these for ClickUp once it's
live." ClickUp is live. List saved. I'm
on it. Blah blah blah. And then we can
also see if we go back, what did it say
to inbox? It said, "Hey, Inbox, you have
a new teammate called Fred. Whenever you
tell a customer a team member will
follow up, you will message Fred with
the customer name, phone number,
address, and then you will put it in
ClickUp as you can see. And now, without
me having to really micromanage that, we
have this new process where next time
Inbox does a sweep of an agent or of
emails that need delegation, it will go
ahead and tell Fred to create that task
in ClickUp automatically. And you'd
obviously need to come in here and you'd
say, "Hey, Fred, you know, we have these
five teammates. Maybe each of the
teammates has a different type of
specialty as far as like some are good
with AC, some are good with other types
of things. And if we gave it a little
bit of a directory as far as who to
assign to what stuff, or maybe we had to
give it an a database to look up to be
able to look at their calendars to see
who can actually um you know, fulfill
it. Then we can start to add more color
into Fred's processes. And just a quick
check on our actual usage, we are now at
13% used up for the week. Real quick,
guys, just wanted to say if you're
enjoying this video and you're enjoying
the way that I teach, please consider
subscribing and joining my free school
community. The link for that is down in
the description. We're building a global
community of AI builders and
entrepreneurs and business owners. We're
almost at 450,000 members. We're almost
at half a million, which is super super
exciting. And it would just mean a lot
to me if you joined. We have a lot of
resources in here. We've got agent
skills. We've got every YouTube video
where I give away free resources. Like I
said, skills, guides, templates, docs,
GitHub repos, I give it all away in here
for completely free. We also have a
7-day challenge. We have a build your
AIOS course. We've got a lot of fun
stuff going on in here. Events,
certification programs, tons of cool
things that we're building towards. So,
if you're enjoying it, if you like the
way I teach, please definitely check it
out. Hope to see you guys in there.
Let's get back to the video. Okay, so so
far we've gotten pretty familiar with
all the stuff. We've talked about all
four of these four C's. We've kind of
used them interchangeably, and now you
should hopefully be understanding how
you're going to keep growing up all four
of these kind of together, right? like
you keep building all of these different
context and connections and capabilities
and cadence as you go and as you add
more bots. We've also talked about a few
hacks like logging things in ClickUp and
building you know like systems around
that. And so I wanted to do one more
piece of that so we get to the place
where we are um with the way that I do
it. So we have a list now in ClickUp
that we can use but right now it only
basically gets delegated whenever an
email comes in that needs to have some
sort of you know person take ownership
over it. But what I think is really
helpful is when you're doing tasks with
any of your agents ever, any project
that you start working on, you are
having it be logged so you can
understand what agents are working on it
and what the status is. So now that
we've connected to ClickUp, I want you
to take ownership over something which
is basically just managing projects
inside of our ClickUp. So what I mean by
that is not only when we are delegating
out emails for one of our team members,
but also when we're doing any sort of
projects, if we're building new agents,
if we are building new Google Sheets or
building new processes or whatever the
project might be, everything that we do
needs to be logged inside of ClickUp for
visibility. I'm talking I want to see
things like what agents did you assign
this to? What time did you do it? Um is
it in progress? Is it complete? When do
we have the due date on it? just
basically so I can at the end of each
week track what actually is being moved
and you know making sure that projects
don't go stale and they don't die and
that we don't forget about things stuff
like that and so what will happen here
is we're able to turn this into a skill
that just happens automatically without
us having to say oh put that in ClickUp
put that in ClickUp so then after you've
been using Grockbot for let's just say a
month you can then go back and see
everything that you've actually done
with these bots and it gives you way
better visibility into how often you're
actually using these. You could also, if
you wanted to, you could add at the end
of every routine. So, by routine, I mean
these things that happen automatically.
If you wanted to, you could go in there
and you could say, um, at the end of
every single run, if you took action,
add this to ClickUp just so we can see
what happened. Now, I just realized when
I switched into here, we had this little
error. So, Gmail signed out. I can't see
new customer mail right now. The only
reason this happened is because I had to
switch my password because I was signing
in on so many different accounts and I
switched my password. Otherwise, that
wouldn't have happened. These should
save, but if you switch your password,
it will probably have you just
reauthorize. So, I'm going to
reauthorize real quick, but I wanted to
address this so not to scare you guys
that you have to like go sign in like
every hour or every day only if you like
actually switch something on the back
end. So, what's happening is the list is
already set up and now friend is just
understanding how to populate this with
actual projects and tasks. Now, remember
what we're going to do is we're going to
turn this into a skill so it just
happens automatically and that doesn't
mean that it's going to be perfect. we
might see some cards come through and be
like, uh, this probably should have been
split into two or, uh, you know, you
didn't give us enough detail. So, for
example, if I go into here, we can see
that we have some in progress, like the
inbox emergency watch every 30 minutes.
This probably doesn't deserve a task
because this happens every single 30
minutes. We also have something like
this. And we can see we have an owner,
we have agents, we have asked, we have
links. I like this. If we didn't like
this description, then we would ask it
to change it. But right now, my only
feedback is these routines that run so
frequently, like every 30 minutes,
probably shouldn't be a task. I think
that having this end of week one is good
because then when the end of week report
comes out, we can mark this as complete.
But we're just going to go ahead and get
rid of that. So, I'm just going to say
that looks great. Two things I want you
to do. The first thing is I want you to
turn this into a skill. So just like a
log to ClickUp skill so that every
single time you actually delegate a
project or you understand that we're
building a new project, you can do this
as a skill and just like it's always
consistent because I like the way that
you have the description set up right
now. But I will say the inbox check
every 30 minutes, I don't think that
deserves to be a task. So if you could
just go ahead and archive that and then
update the skill because we're going to
have to as we build more projects help
you build your understanding of what
deserves a task in ClickUp or not. But I
do like how you are basically being safe
rather than sorry and logging more
rather than less. So take that feedback
and make those changes and build that
skill. And what you'll notice on the
lefth hand side is that we just got a
message from inbox. You can see here
that it said, okay, this basically was
my scan for every 30 minutes. No new
emergencies. The morning pile is still
there and the rest of Google security
notes from reconnecting. I'll keep
watching. And what you can do now is you
can see how often these routines have
run. So, if I click into this one, you
can see that we had one run 34 minutes
ago and then we had run one run 5
minutes ago. So, this is where you can
just get visibility into if these are
actually going on and if everything's
running as it should be. If you want to
test them out, you could click test run
up here and it will just fire right
away. If you want to deactivate them,
you can just basically pause them by
turning this off. As you can see, it
disabled this routine. But I don't want
to disable that. So, I'm just going to
go ahead and turn that back on. And if
you wanted to delete them, you can just
go ahead and delete them right there.
But now we can see that friend actually
created a skill called log to clickup
which is perfect. We could come in here
and make little adjustments if we need
to. And we can see that the 30 minute
watch card is archived. So that no
longer exists in our board. Perfect.
Everything is assigned here. We've got
priority. We've got due dates. That is
all looking good. Now one thing you guys
probably noticed when we were inside of
my actual Grockbot is I had different
like folders and I had some group chats
and stuff. So really all I did there was
if you right click on an agent and you
put move to new section, you can kind of
organize them by section. And in here I
can call this, let's just say um I'm
just going to call this general for now.
So then as you build up teams of like
sales agents and um marketing agents and
recruiting agents, you can kind of box
them up just for organization and then
you can close them out because like I
said, a lot of times you won't be in
these threads. You're more so going to
be dealing with like your seuite or your
executives. And then something else you
can do is you can actually create
channels. Let's say you wanted to have
one channel just for all your bots. You
could put a new channel. You can have a
group chat with everybody. And this is
just going to say all hands. And now you
can talk to all three of them at once.
Now, I don't think this is necessarily
needed in this example because these
bots can all talk to each other either
way. But maybe if you wanted to have
like all of your different leadership
team in one channel so that every week
you could get a report on like what
happened in their vertical or whatever
the use case might be. You want to see
everything they've done that week or you
want to get everyone's opinion on
something and give them a better
environment to talk as a group chat
rather than just like one-on-one DMs
between all the agents. Then that's how
you do it. You just have a channel like
this. Hey guys, this is currently
everyone that we've have on the team. Is
there anything else that you think right
now we need to build? Are you guys
identifying any opportunities for new
skills or new routines? Or more
specifically, based on what you know
about me and our business and our
current workflows, what other agents
might be helpful for us to keep growing
our business? Now, one thing I'm curious
about is if they are going to be aware
that we haven't yet connected our
calendar because that's like a big part
of it, right? Like we have um where is
it? Where' it go? We have this Google
calendar here which is Nate Herk8. So,
it should be like, you know, my personal
calendar, but they haven't had any
visibility into it yet because if I go
back in here, the plugin for the
calendar is actually different. It's not
the same as Google Drive. It's a
separate plugin. So, I'm just curious if
they're able to identify, hey, you know,
that might be one good gap to save you
more time. Nate is if we could see your
calendar. So, you can see here inbox
came in with some stuff about the inbox
and looking at what types of, you know,
tickets are coming in. Friend says inbox
is right. We don't need another email
person. The whole is about booking. Fred
comes in and says, "Yeah, I already
filed those promised calls. They stood
on blah blah blah. One cheap thing I can
own without a new agent is a weekday
check of open emergency call backs."
Fred says, "Okay, go ahead and do it."
Inbox quotes, reply skill, Fred's call
back check, then a dispatch agent, Nate,
say the word, and we'll build out an
order, blah, blah, blah. So, they have
kind of been able to talk based on what
they're able to see and based on their
area of expertise and help kind of like
make decisions and ideulate. So this is
the way that I would think about first
of all maybe you you go out here and you
create a COO and you create um a CMO and
you have them understand high level what
is their goal and what are they supposed
to be helping you drive towards and then
you put them in a conversation where
you're constantly saying okay what do we
do this week what happened where did we
have bottlenecks where should we be
building new agents and where should we
be looking to have automations and once
again outsource the thinking but don't
outsource the understanding don't
blindly just say yep looks good do it
only do these things if you think it
will actually provide value and give you
more leverage in your day-to-day. And
the reason why that's so important is
because there's a difference here
between the shared memory of your agents
and the specific memory. So, let me just
show you that. If I go to friend and I
say, "Hey, so I'm just trying to
understand what do you and all my other
Grockbots know about me. What is the
difference between what you specifically
know about me and what all Grockbots
know?" Because there's, like I said,
individual agent memory per agent and
then there's like a shared memory. So
friend, because I've talked to him the
most, probably knows more about me than
inbox and Fred do. So for example, if I
go to Fred, hey Fred, can you tell me
what specifically you know about me that
other agents might not? And then what is
like the overall global memory that you
know about me and my business and this
whole ecosystem? So friend says, yeah,
two notebooks. Everyone on your team
knows your name, Twin Cities, Chicago
Time, keep explanations simple, and that
your Google is Nate Herk. That's the
shared stuff. friend knows other stuff
like summit is HVAC small team honest no
upsell shop inbox as email Fred is
clickup inbox and Fred have their own
notes for their jobs and they don't
automatically know everything I know. So
the point I'm trying to make here is
when you're building up all these agents
and when you have them in a group chat
like this they're coming from different
places. They have different
perspectives. They don't natively see
inside of each people's channels. So,
make sure you're orchestrating that your
like executives, as we talked about
here, that your executives know a lot
about you and that the operators only
need to know pretty much what they need
to know for that specific job. So, Fred
only needs to know if I get an email or
if I get a message from inbox, I have to
do X, Y, and Z in X, Y, and Z order.
Fred doesn't necessarily need to know
what are our marketing goals for the
next quarter or, you know, how much
revenue are we making every month. I'm
not going to read this whole thing out,
but you can see this is what Fred
responded with. All right, so let's go
back and talk about some connections for
a sec. If I go to the plugins, you can
see that there is a lot of stuff here.
There's featured things, there is, you
know, MCP things, there's payments,
there's a lot, but there's also a lot
that you can't access. Like for me
specifically, I would love to connect my
Grockbots to my YouTube channel, which I
cannot currently do. They would just
have to do it through native web search.
I would also want to connect them to
maybe something like our company
LinkedIn, which we cannot do right here.
So, one solution to that is we can use
something called Composeio, which says
connect and operate a thousand plus apps
right from here. So, what I'm going to
do is I'm going to go ahead and click
add Composeio. What you're going to do
is you're going to go to Composeio and
you're going to create an account. And
what that will look like is this. And
it's completely free to create, which is
awesome. And now inside of Composeio,
you have all of these different things
you can connect. And right away, you see
some of the most highest leverage ones
for me are we get to connect YouTube and
we can connect LinkedIn. If I go ahead
here and search, we can see LinkedIn is
active. We can see that we could also
connect something like QuickBooks, which
is really helpful. You can connect a lot
more through something like Composeio
that has all these different servers to
connect. And once you've connected it
inside of here, it automatically syncs
to Grockbot once you tell it to. So, I'm
going to authenticate into Composeio.
We're going to pull up this account real
quick. Awesome. So, we are authorized
into Composeio. I come back into here
and click on connected. There we go. And
now if I go back into friend and say,
"Hey, I want you to look at our new
plugin called um Composeio and I need
you to just see what apps inside of
there you can actually access." Now,
what's cool about plugins is plugins and
skills and the whole like little
browser, those are universal across all
your agents. So every single agent that
you spin up can use Composio and can use
everything that you've connected.
Whereas the memory is what differs by
agent. So you connect it once, all your
agents can touch it, which is great. So
you can see inside of Composeio, we are
connected to LinkedIn, QuickBooks,
YouTube, and Perplexity. So now if I
said, okay, whenever you're doing
research, I want you to use Perplexity
within Composeio. Whenever you're
looking at YouTube stuff, you would go
here to YouTube. And now we can also
access this other stuff if we wanted to.
And then what I would want to do is say,
can you just make sure that you add this
to the shared memory so that every
single agent in the future understands
that these four apps are currently
authenticated inside of Composeio
because I want them in the future if
they need to touch it, they need to know
where it all lives. And so this is the
point I was trying to make about the
connections, but not only these
connections, we are now giving it the
context to understand where these
connections live. And then that helps us
power even more capabilities and cadence
as you guys can see. So, it's just going
to go ahead and update that shared
memory so that every future agent
understands this. Now, what you've
noticed about what we've started to
build here is we're building a lot of
things like knowledge work. I like using
this kind of stuff for things that are
quick tasks, project management,
creating resources, approving things,
checking things, task based things
rather than building production apps or
software. So earlier I talked about sort
of like what are some things that I
might use like cloud code for um or
codeex for versus using something like a
Hermes or more of like a personal agent
or agent army type of deal. Well, I
personally would use cloud code for more
things like um building like apps or
custom software or building websites or
games. If I wanted to be able to do this
stuff on the go, I would do more things
like I said, you know, triaging the
inbox or automatic like research reports
and, you know, maybe even like creating
marketing assets because we can connect
this to different things to create like
carousels or LinkedIn post or Instagram
reels, all of that type of stuff as
well. But really, if I wanted to build
websites and apps, I would want to have
more of a traditional like coding
harness that I can connect to GitHub and
have GitHub connect to my Verscell and I
can constantly be pulling in these new
code bases and things because we have
more control over like sessions and
context rot and controlling what goes in
and controlling what we're looking at.
It just is much better at staying
organized on building legit software and
websites and things like that compared
to something like this which can get
messy pretty quick if you're doing like
super high-risk work like that because
it's even more vibe coding here than it
would be if you were opening up cloud
code or codecs. But that doesn't mean it
couldn't happen. Like I have agents
inside of mine that are building me
little landing pages that are simple. Or
I have one that's like they're building
me these HTML reports and they're
putting it on an actual URL so that I
can just get my end of week report on my
phone and I can view it and it looks
cleaner than just looking at like a
markdown file or something like that.
And what's cool about that is if you
find GitHub repos that have skills or
projects or other things that you want
to play with, you can still do that
inside of Grockbot. So, Hyperframes
helps agents write HTML and it renders
it into video, which is probably
something that a lot of us need for our
websites or for marketing assets, but
maybe a lot of us don't have like a
video editing team or have any
experience editing videos. So, let me
just show you a quick little hack of
what you can do with something like
Hyperframes. So, I'm just going to go
ahead and I'm going to add a new agent
here and I'm going to add a new bot. And
we're just going to create a new bot.
This one is going to be specifically
just like a video editor. So one it said
it's gonna so this one's going to come
back and say hey what can I do for you
and we are going to just kind of set
this thing up. You are going to be my
video editor. Your name is going to be
slice. What I want you to do is
investigate this GitHub repo and pull
this stuff in so that you can actually
use the hyperframe skills and understand
what hyperframes does. And then you're
going to actually write HTML and create
a video for us. This video, I want it to
be like a 15-second like sizzle reel
that we can put on our website as far as
like who we are, what we do, and how to
work with us. And for the how to work
with us call to action, just say book a
call. Just put a fake number on there
for now. Actually, if you have this real
data, which you can get from messaging
friend, he's the chief of staff in this
organization. Then reach out to him and
see what real data you have to work with
and then create us the deliverable. Here
is that hyperframes GitHub repo. Cool.
So now this was us showing how we
actually created a bot ourselves rather
than having friend make one for us and
it's a very similar process. It's
basically just onboarding giving one
specific role and hopefully all of this
stuff should be set up. You can see that
it just named itself slice and we have a
description which is you are the video
editor for Nate. You build short HTML
hyperframe videos for Summit Home
Services starting with website Sizzle
Reels. So that's pretty specific. I
could basically just get rid of that
part and just say yeah you build short
videos for Summit Home Services. And
then I'm just going to give this guy a
quick tag so that we can keep ourselves
a little bit more organized. And I might
even just move this guy into a new
folder or section. And we'll call this
one content. Actually, no, we'll just
call this marketing because that's a bit
more broad. So now we have a marketing
folder that we're starting to build out.
And what this might trigger us to do is
instead of having friend manage slice,
we might want to make like a CMO. And
then we could create like a LinkedIn bot
and we could create um like a Photoshop
bot. And then whenever we want to do
stuff in the marketing folder, we have
our CMO be sort of like our point of
contact to delegate work out that way.
Same way you would do with like finance
and accounting and same way you might do
with just general operations and things
like that too. And you can see already
that Slice has been messaging friend to
make sure that it's going to put legit
factual information about the business
inside of our video. All right, so you
can see that we had both Friend and
Slice message us about this video. It's
done. It's 15 seconds. But what friend
did is it gave me a link right here
which actually goes to ClickUp. So if I
follow this link, it takes us to this
completed project. So that just shows
you that it was able to understand,
okay, we need to log this in ClickUp so
that Nate can see that later. And we
actually have the deliverable, we have
the agent, we have, you know, all of
this information about it. And now if I
go back into the Grockbot, we actually
want to go watch that real quick. So
I'll go into Slice. It sent us the video
right here. I'll click play. We have
Summit Home Services, Twin Cities
Heating, Cooling, and Water Services. So
that is real. We fix it. We don't sell
you a system you need. So that aligns
with what we said. You can notice the
background is green as well, which
follows our guidelines that I told I
think I told inbox that earlier and it
must have relayed that to friend, but
something just happened here. It
couldn't load media. And that happens
around the like 12 second mark. I'm not
sure why that is, but you can see that
this is a sizzle.mpp4. So like I said,
I'm not exactly sure why that happened.
Maybe a rendering error. But what you
guys might be wondering at this point is
where are all of these deliverables
being saved? You know, sometimes we're
creating things like a Google sheet, in
which case we're getting it stored in
the cloud in Google. But what about when
we're creating these MP4s or when we're
creating markdown files or the knowledge
files, all the stuff that we've talked
about, where does that live? And that's
where if we open up the computer, we can
see that they do have something right
here called the file manager. And in
here, we can see that we have this
workspace and we have videos. We have
the weekly email report Python scripts.
We have a weekly email report, Excel
sample, we have hyperframe skills. So
what it did is it manages this and it
saves things. So the GitHub repo that I
gave it earlier, this hyperframes one,
it pulled in what it needed from like
the cloud files and the skill files and
it saved this in its local file
directory that every agent can use,
which is pretty cool. And it also saved
the video right here. If I go here, the
Summit Sizzle, this is where it should
have saved the MP4. Um, if I go to the
renders, we can see that it lives right
in there. That's the MP4 file. So, this
is where all this stuff lives. If I
actually go ahead and um, open this up.
I'm not sure if it's going to let us
open this up in anything. I'll try
Google Chrome.
And there we go. It actually lets us
open it up right here. And now we can
see that we get past that little
rendering error. Good. So, that's where
that loaded up. And once again, all of
your agents can access this stuff. So,
the same way that if you're on, you
know, if you're on Mac, you've got your
Finder. If you're on Windows, you've got
your uh file explorer, and what we're
building towards is a local file
directory of all of this context. So,
this is what mine looks like. You know
how earlier I talk a lot about this AIOS
with our context and our connections and
all this stuff? This is what mine looks
like. If you guys have been following my
channel for a while, you've probably
heard me talk about my Herk 2, which has
everything about my business, about me.
Uh, it can touch everything. It knows
the business and our goals better than I
do, honestly. And it's just a collection
of files and folders. I've got my Herk
Brain. I've got all of these other
worlds. I've got um a projects folder.
And inside of the projects folder, it's
all the projects we work on. As well as
in here, one of the projects is called
YouTube videos. And this is a bunch of
stuff that I do for all my other YouTube
videos. So, this is a massive folder
with a bunch of files. And the cool
thing is I can give that this whole file
or sorry, I can give this whole folder
to different agents. You know, actually
if I come to my repos in my GitHub, this
is my Herk 2 project, which means I
could give this link to my agent, which
is what I did for my actual Grockbot,
and I could say, "Hey, can you just like
clone this locally?" So then this whole
workspace could look just like my actual
Herk 2 that lives on my real desktop
right here. And like I said, all the
agents can actually use this. So, if I
leave out of here and I go to friend and
I open up his computer and he has a
different Chrome tab pulled up, but if I
go to the um file manager, they can all
work together here. But what you need is
you probably need to instruct them to
have some sort of system in here that
they can all share together because
remember how we talked about the shared
memory and the agent specific memory? If
you had more shared context in here,
they could all reach it. So, that's one
thing that I want to quickly tell friend
about. I want you to create a bit of a
better folder structure inside of your
local file directory since all of the
agents can work out of there. I want you
just for now to set up a folder called
context and to set up a folder called
projects. And whenever we're creating
new projects, just store them in a new
folder in the projects folder. And right
now just put in some base information
about me and about our business and just
give some context in there. And over
time as we need to grow that, that's
where you guys should be saving work in
this sort of local file directory
structure. So anyways, the reason I
wanted to point that out is just so you
understood where is all of the stuff
going because if you have something
making like an HTML every Friday or
markdown reports every day, those are
being stored somewhere that the agents
can touch. And it's important that you
at least understand that you can come in
here and you can click through yourself.
And also that when agents are passing
work around, they can basically like
give each other the file paths of
different reports or different docs. And
that's how they can more effectively
communicate and share work and
contribute to the same stuff. But it is
important to think about the way you
want to set that up, the structure you
want as far as maybe you just start with
a big folder called projects and later
you make that more organized. However
you and your team will typically work on
like a shared drive or a Google Drive or
however you want to store data. Just
think about either doing it locally or
maybe in Google Drive or in notion or
maybe all three. Just be aware of where
your data is actually going and where
your projects live. You can see that it
just started to build that out. And if I
open this up, we now have a folder
called context and we have some markdown
files with gaps and summit and the team
and me. And then if I go back, we also
have projects and it put in like the
sizzle reel and other projects that we
build will go in here as well. And it
also went into ClickUp and logged that
as something that we just did. So, if I
go in here and I show completed tasks,
you can see that it set up the shared
context and projects folders. So, as I
was editing this video, I realized that
the Hyperframes video that I showed you
guys was just really boring and really
bad. And hyperframes actually is pretty
cool when you build some skills around
it. So, just to show you a quick example
that you can actually get some pretty
solid motion graphics in here. This is
how I use hyperframes for some YouTube
videos to create intros and to also
create things like um some open loops.
If you see like this full video, I was
able to prompt it enough so it
understands the style where I want it to
animate these flowcharts and it keeps
like these like spatial elements. As you
can see, it's going to move on to number
two in this list right here. You can see
that it takes this whole flowchart, puts
it back into the box, and then we're
going to go into two, three, four, five.
So, um, it's just pretty cool when you
really start to prompt it and build some
skills around it. It is pretty solid.
So, I just wanted to show that off real
quick. But then I went ahead and asked
Aaron, our CMO, to make another one. And
you can see that it actually delegated
around with Slice and Studio to create
like different images for B-roll and
also logos and stuff. And then Slice
came back and made the actual video. So
if I come in here real quick to Aaron's
screen, I'll just give this a quick
play.
So, I mean, this is nothing
groundbreaking at all, but if you don't
have a team where you can afford a video
editor right now and you take a couple
iterations using the bike method I
talked about, you can really get some
pretty cool stuff done just in here with
a few different agents. Now, one use
case that I think is really good to do
with that is to have an agent that is
always like reading your meetings. So
whether you use Granola or you use um
Fathom or Google Meet or you know
Fireflies, which is what I'm currently
using, having an agent do that. So what
I want to show you is an agent that I
use myself. We're going to create a new
bot. And what we're going to do for this
bot is connected to Fireflies. And all
we have to do is log in. And what I want
to do is at the end of every weekday,
because I usually only have calls on
weekdays, what I wanted to do is grab
the transcripts from those meetings from
that day and then put it into a folder
locally that is like meeting recordings.
And maybe that's organized by quarter or
by month, but I want those transcripts
to be stored in there so that all of my
agents can see that and have context of
like some of the important meetings that
I'm going in because that context is
really good for your business, for
making decisions, for understanding
priorities and stuff like that. So, you
are going to be my meeting bot. Your
name is Fireflies. Basically, what's
going to happen is I need to authorize
into Fireflies because that software has
all of the transcripts from my meetings.
And then at the end of every day, I need
you to set up a routine. Let's just say
6 p.m. every single day. Um, weekdays,
sorry, 6 p.m. on weekdays where you're
going in, you're pulling all the
transcripts and you're storing them in
our local file directory. So, you should
probably create a new folder in there
called meetings. And I want you to
organize that by month. And then, yeah,
you're basically just storing in the
transcripts of my meetings every single
weekday, putting it in there so that our
other agents can always pull from that
if they need context on certain calls.
And you are going to go by the name
fire. And so, that's really the beauty
of it. I have one very specific type of
task and automation that I want to set
up. So, I just make a new bot. I
instruct it what to do. It's going to
build a routine. I'm going to
authenticate into Fireflies. And you
just keep scaling up different
capabilities and different cadence
things just like that. And I think the
toughest part about this stuff a lot of
times is figuring out what are the good
use cases rather than like how does the
tech work. It's more about what are the
use cases that actually help. And I
think a really good way to think about
that is just by thinking about the
triggers. Meaning what happens in your
business that triggers you to do
something. Whether that's time based or
whether that's event based. So are there
any things that I have to do on Mondays
or Fridays or Wednesdays after I have a
meeting? Is there anything I do every
time? You know, um when I get this type
of email, what do I do? When you think
about the triggers and you understand if
X happens, do I always do Y? Then that's
a really good opportunity to set up some
sort of bot for an automation there. So
it set up its name as fire. It's
currently unassigned. I'm just going to
move this to the general folder. Um it's
created the routine right here, weekday
fireflies dump. And now I need to add
the Fireflies connector. So I said,
"Yep, go ahead and authorize that up."
So once again, it's just as simple as
signing into your account. And luckily,
there was a native plugin for this.
Otherwise, we'd have to try to find it
with something like Composeio or a
different sort of like MCP server
aggregator. And now it's just going to
go ahead and make sure that that
connection actually works. And it told
me it was going to grab everything
that's already in Firefly. So I'm just
going to go ahead and say only grab five
just to prove the concept. And you can
see that I was able to actually
interrupt and steer the direction
because otherwise it was probably going
to start crawling through who knows how
many, maybe like a hundred transcripts.
And I know that was going to take a
while. So I was able to interrupt it
because I watched it and I saw that it
was going down the wrong path. And
that's why it's important to be watching
them because each chain of thought, it's
basically telling you what it needs to
do. And that's good because then, like I
said, you can steer it in the right way
before it starts wasting more of your
tokens. Because if it was going to waste
30 minutes and a bunch of our session
limit, as you can see, we're at 30% now
by just like doing something that you're
not even going to use at the end of the
day, then you want to stop it before it
gets too late. Awesome. So, that has
come through. Let's just go ahead and
make sure that it actually created this
correctly in our file explorer. We're
connecting to the browser. We're going
to open this up. We can see we have
meetings and now we have August of 2026.
And this is where we can view those
markdown files if we needed to. And now
we have a system set up where this is
actually going to do that automatically
at the end of every single day at 6 PM
on weekdays. All right, so I think it's
time that we need to build a CMO. So I'm
just going to create a new bot real
quick. This is going to be our chief
marketing officer, and it's going to
help us create one more bot that's going
to sort of like work and report to the
CMO, which is going to help us create
marketing assets. And I'm talking things
like pictures and images and ads and
things like that. So let's go ahead and
get this spun up.
You are my chief marketing officer. We
are going to call you Aaron. E R I N.
And your job is to help me pretty much
stay on top of things like marketing,
right? Like video editing, um at some
point creating content at scale,
analyzing content, marketing strategy,
growth, stuff like that. So, the first
thing I need you to do is I need you to
help me spin up a designer agent. This
designer agent is going to help with
really just creating photos and videos
for us. So that's what I want you to do
for now. Okay. So as this is getting
spun up, you can see that it just
created a new agent called studio which
I'm going to go ahead and move to the
marketing section. Um Grock has
something called Grock Imagine and that
helps you natively right in here create
photos and videos and stuff like that.
So what I'm going to do is just say um
wait for a specific brief and then I'm
going to say go ahead and have studio
create an image for the whole marketing
team. So, one for Studio, one for Slice,
and one for you, just like profile
pictures for our Grockbot account. And
we're going to see how these come out.
But there's a way to get a lot better
models and way more. So, there's a thing
called Key AI, which is free to sign up
and then you have to put in credits to
actually use it because it's an API. But
in here, we have access to a ton of
different models, video and image, and
also like music. If I go to the API
market, you can see that we can get um
you know like Google models, we can get
Juan, we can get Grock, we can get
Gemini, obviously that's a Google model.
We can get Opus, we can get VO. So if I
go to like uh text to video, you can see
that we get all of these like Cance. If
I go to text to image, we get GBT image
2, which is my favorite one. It's
personally what I use for pretty much
everything. Where'd it go? GBT image 2
right down here. So we have the ability
now to connect Grockbot to this so that
we have way more flexibility with what
models we want to use rather than just
being locked into Grock imagines
ecosystem. So in order to do this though
this is where composio really comes into
play because if I go to plugins there's
no key AI. There is something like
Higsfield which is a very similar type
of tool but this one's a little bit more
expensive but Higfield is also pretty
solid. I've made some other videos with
Higfield before. So, what we're going to
do is because we're already connected to
Composio. If I go back into Composeio,
which is right up here, they have KAI,
which is amazing. So, I'm able to
connect right here to Composio and Key.
I have to do this by getting an API key
for key. So, all you have to do is go
into KAI. You're going to go to API
keys, and you're going to generate a new
key right here, which is kind of just
like a password. So, what I would do is
I would create a new key. I would just
call this one my Grockbot key. I want
all models by default. Create that. And
then I take this value, copy that, and
go ahead and put it in here. Whatever
the tab is, where'd it go? This one
that's asking for our API key for key
connect our account. And now when we go
back into Grock, we should be able to
have it use Composio to use key. So what
I'm going to do is say, okay, so
Studio's on that. What we also just did
is I connected
um key.ai inside of Composeio, and that
gives us access to way better image
models. So what I want you to do is send
studio another task to do the same
thing, three profile pictures, but this
time do it twice. So do it with GBT
image 2 and then also do it with Nano
Banana 2. So we can just compare these
different AI models and which ones we
actually like the best. And it didn't
spell key AI right. So I'm just going to
go ahead and fix that. But it should be
able to have found that either way with
context. But anyways, we're going to go
ahead and shoot that off. Oh, and you
can see Studio already changed its
profile picture. You can see here studio
created this picture and changed it
because what happens is inside of here
when you edit the avatar you can
generate images you can upload or you
can use the bot ones and so studio
actually proactively made the image and
then changed it as well. So that's just
to show not only can you create pictures
like that and this is Gro imagine but
you can also do things like creating
marketing assets. Let's say you were
building like you had an e-commerce
brand or whatever. You could create
different product shots, different
marketing assets, different ads, things
like that. And now that we have key, we
get access to better models because once
these other ones come in, I'm assuming
you guys will see how the other models
in my mind are better. So it sent studio
the same message and now it's doing it
with two other image models. So I will
let you know when these come back. Okay,
this is actually interesting. So what
happened is the connection to key.ai AI
doesn't actually allow these agents to
make an image. So, I'm not sure if it's
because the way Composio connects or
what. So, we basically have two options.
We could use the API documentation in
here and we could basically just have
key use its CLI to hit the API. That's
one thing. That's one workaround that
you could try. But what else you can do
because we understand that it's able to
use browser use. All I have to do is I
can open up the desktop and it's opening
it up right now. And I can just go ahead
and sign into key.ai AI because this is
also a headed interface. So right here
you can see that it lets you choose the
model. It lets you put in your prompt
and then go ahead and generate these
assets. So what I'm going to do is just
sign in once to key.ai and then studio
this agent should be able to figure out
how to navigate here in order to still
generate the assets that we're looking
for which is going to give us the end
result that we want. So a little bit of
a um workaround that we had to do but as
you can see because of the computer use
and there's other ways to work around
when you can't find the right
connection. Cool. Now you can see that I
am signed into this account. So now we
just have to wait for Studio to learn
the interface and click around, put in
the prompts and get those assets for us.
Okay, so that took a little while
because Studio had to get in here and it
had to learn the interface and it was
trying to generate these in parallel by
having different tabs open, which was
good. I'm glad that it did that, but it
still had to learn the interface a
little bit. And so honestly, that could
have been a good use case of teaching a
task if I said, "Hey, give me the
prompts. I'm going to come into here.
I'm going to show you how you navigate,
where you put the prompts in, how you
generate these, how you save them, and
then it turns that into a skill. So,
that is something I'm going to say real
quick is just now that you've navigated
the interface of key and you've
understood how to generate different
types of images with different types of
models, it would be very similar if you
did videos. So, I just want you to save
that as a skill so that next time we
need generations, you're able to just
navigate the interface quicker and, you
know, just give me the the outputs
quicker. So, anyways, good job. Build
that skill. So now we're going to have
that turned into a skill. Whenever you
do something that you might do again,
just turn it into a skill. It's ra you'd
rather be safe than sorry there. So I
got this message back from Aaron. Aaron
is the CMO if you guys remember.
Actually, you know what? I'll just go
ahead and give her the tag because we
don't yet have that. So anyways, we got
that message back from Aaron. It says
both sets are in and it hasn't yet
installed any of them. So these are the
three from GBT image 2. You can see that
the prompting was consistent in a way
where these two women look the same.
These two women look similar, but these
two men look very different. Um, but
they have similar backgrounds, right?
They've got like the the green style
with the little like kind of light
behind. This one has like these yellow
streaks. We have GBT image 2, like I
said, and Nano Banana 2. You can see the
styling is different. I'm assuming it
used the same prompts for all three.
Maybe a little bit different, like I
said, or maybe these prompts weren't as
specific. But anyways, now we can just
choose which ones we like best. And for
now, I'm just going to go ahead and
actually just say Nano Banana 2 because
I think these look a little bit more
like they were trying to be realistic,
whereas these look a little bit more
like I don't know, just like agent
profile pictures. So, I'll just go ahead
and say Nano Banana 2. It will relay
that message down. And then our
marketing team, Aaron, Studio, and Slice
will all have different profile
pictures. And so, what happens here is
it has to message each agent
individually to do it. As you can see,
Studio changed theirs. And if I go to
slice, it says, "Hey, Nate wants this to
be your Grockbot profile picture. Please
set it now." And look what it did. It
gave it the file path. Meaning, if I
actually go into Slice, for example, it
gave it the exact file path. So, Slice
opened up its computer. It went into
here, it found the pro the portraits,
and then it chose this picture and set
this as its own um profile picture. So
that's just another example of how it's
saving things locally and the agents are
able to pass work around because they
have that shared computer. So I wanted
to show you guys another use case for
this sort of routine thing that I think
a lot of you guys will find very helpful
if you are living in Slack and even if
you're not it's good to know about
because like I said this the Grockbot
stuff is going to get more capable and
more capable. So what I just want to
show you is this bot. What I want to do
is I'm just going to start off by
calling this guy Slack.
And we are just going to say your job is
to respond to Slack messages from the
team and give them, you know, any
information that you need or create
tasks or delegate the workar around. You
are basically the touch point from Slack
to the Grockbot ecosystem. So just a
really simple agent that we're going to
set up here. And what we're going to do
is we're going to create a routine. And
instead of triggering this based on um
time, we're going to trigger this based
on a Slack message, which is pretty
cool. So, whenever there are new
messages, it could be either when the
bot is mentioned or reaction added to
message. So, for now, I'm just going to
do new messages. And we're going to put
in the channel, which if I open my
Slack, we're going to be looking at this
one, YouTube testing Nate. So, I'm going
to put in the name of the channel, which
like I said, YouTube testing Nate. And
any text is containing. So it could be
very specific like maybe we are only
asking for like a Grockbot or whatever
or like I said if you wanted to have it
be a mention but just very simply that's
what I'm going to do and the routine is
basically Slack message and your job is
to on a new message in the Slack team
channel to delegate to the right agent
to get the information you need to be as
helpful as possible to the team in Slack
as you can. So very simple we're just
going to do that and now that is an
active routine. So what happens is
obviously we haven't connected Slack
yet. So we're going to have to do that.
So I'm going to click on yes connect it.
Now one thing about this is this has to
be Slack inside of your organization or
if you know the organization like if
you're an external connection into a
different org they have to be able to
add cursor. They have to be able to add
cursorbot to the Slack channel otherwise
it's not going to work. So you can't
just insert your Grock bots into every
Slack channel you're in. You have to
have some level of like admin
permissioning inside that Slack channel.
So for internal Slack it's going to work
great. You say hey everybody there is
now a Grockbot in this channel. If you
guys want to talk to it, just message it
or message this specific channel, blah
blah blah, and it will respond. So, you
have to now authorize Slack. Of course,
it's going to take up to this page right
here. For example, you can see that I'm
not authorized to add one inside of my
channel with Smooth Media. So, that's
not going to work unless I reached out
to them and asked them to install it.
What I'm going to do is just go back
into my actual one that we own right
here. And then I'm going to say that we
review and we approve these permissions.
So, I'll click allow. And that works.
Now, what we're going to have to do is
in the actual channel, we have to invite
cursor. So, I'm actually running into
issues with this because I have a
different cursor account and I'm trying
to do this demo with this Grock account
with this Slack account. So, I'm just
going to go ahead and play a clip of how
this actually works. It's super simple.
Like I said, it's just this. You just
have to have the right accounts
authenticated in. So, I'll play that
clip real quick. So, here's the Slack
card that popped up. I'm going to go
ahead and authorize into Slack real
quick. It's asking what Slack channels
it should treat as home base. I'm going
to ask it what channels can you actually
see and read. because if you're like me
in Slack, you might be in a ton of
different workspaces and channels and
things like that. So, it's just worth
seeing what it actually knows. Now, look
at this. It basically was only able to
see some of the stuff inside one
workspace, but I have another email with
some other channels I'm in, right? So, I
said, "Hey, I want to connect another
one." And it just lets you add another
one. So, here we have a default
connection, but now I also have one that
I'm calling work, and I can sign in with
a different account here so that I can
use different channels. There we go.
Now, I have authenticated another Slack
account, and it should be able to see
everything that I'm doing in there. now,
which is great. Now, my Grockbot can see
into all of these public channels as
well as these private channels in DMs,
which is just great. So, what I want you
to do is help me set up a routine that's
on a Slack trigger. So, inside of the
default Slack workspace, what I want you
to do is when you get a message from the
um YouTube testing Nate channel, I want
that to trigger you to basically give me
a notification on what happened. So,
let's see if it's able to understand
what I'm saying and create us a routine
inside of its settings that's based on a
trigger rather than a timebased routine.
Okay, cool. So, it created a routine
called YouTube testing Nate alerts.
Perfect. You can see right here it says
when to run on new messages in the
YouTube testing Nate channel. So, it
founded the right channel. It created
the right trigger and it set up the
actual instruction. So, before this
works, it says one setup step. So, it
actually fires is in that channel you
have to run /invite atcursor. So, let me
just copy this command. The channel
listeners only hear channels the cursor
Slack app is in. So, let me just go
ahead and try that real quick. I'm
inviting at cursor. There we go. It was
just added. And now in here, let's say,
hey, a new sponsorship deal has come in
for $1,000 million billion dollars for
um a YouTube video. The company is
called Chipotle. Okay, so I shot that
off. Let's see what's going on inside of
Grockbot. Okay, so we're seeing that
it's having the little newbot is working
animation. It says newbot because I
haven't named this yet. I haven't
touched anything besides sending that
message in Slack. Boom. New in YouTube
testing. Nate, you posted that a
Chipotle YouTube sponsorship deal came
in for this much money. Cool. So, that's
how you can see that that routine is
working and that got set up so quickly.
With Niten, that might have taken me
maybe 15 minutes. With Claude code, that
might have taken me like seven minutes.
With this, this took like 2 minutes and
one prompt. It's pretty insane. But now
you have something in your Slack channel
that your team can message and then on
the back end it can look up data. It can
message other agents. It can create
assets and then send that back to you in
Slack. And one other thing I wanted to
throw out there is I know that some of
you guys might not love the idea of
having a completely new interface to
learn and to manage. And what you can do
is you could also just think about
Grockbot as your environment to develop
different agents. And those automations
can just feed into whatever front end
you already use. So for example, I built
this one new bot called X. And what I
wanted to do is every day give me a
summary like kind of like a daily AI
roundup from X. But what I did here is
instead of having it send it back to me
in Grockbot, let's say I didn't want it
there. Let's say I use Slack or I wanted
to send me an email or whatever. In this
case, I had it do ClickUp. And so what I
did is I signed in with a different
ClickUp account so that in my ClickUp I
actually get a DM. And so you can see I
have a DM coming here from Upai. And now
I get this AI daily brief for Sunday,
August 30th where I can see different
things. I also can get links to the
actual X post when it pulls it, which is
pretty cool. Um, and I can see all this
stuff and it also told me exactly how
much this was going to spend. It's about
half a cent per post and it pulls in
obviously a decent amount of posts and
it will tell us how much we have left in
our account and things like that. And by
the way, this is just using the default
plugin right here for X, which is what's
going to charge you per usage. There are
some other ways you can scrape X with
different APIs and stuff, but if you use
the native one, it's pretty cool because
you can also get your own profile stats.
So, I could say, can you please take a
look at my post on X and also anything
that I've bookmarked just to give me a
rundown of what's on my account because
this will obviously authenticate in same
way. And now you can also do things on
your own account. And you can also build
automations where if you bookmark a ton
of stuff throughout the week, maybe at
the end of every week, it could pull in
all the posts that you've bookmarked and
it could remind you that those are there
and it can do extra research for you and
just kind of make sure you don't forget
about those things. But really, the
point I was trying to make here was less
about X. It was more about if you don't
want those routines to always message
you in Grockbot, you can say, "Hey, send
this to my email or send this to my
Slack channel or whatever you want to
connect." You can have it do things in
other places for you. You could maybe
just treat this more as like the quote
unquote developer interface and then you
can have the automations obviously have
the data destination be somewhere else
somewhere where you're already using it
more let's just say dayto-day. And
speaking of X, I made this post on X a
few weeks ago and Elon Musk retweeted it
with a little message. So if you guys
want to see him hop on my podcast, then
go spam him in this X post. Thank you
very much. Okay, so the last thing that
I want to talk about are bot templates.
Now, excuse the hair. I just got out of
the shower, so it doesn't look as good
as it normally does. But anyways, bot
template. So, this is pretty cool. When
you come into any of the Grock bots,
whether they are pinned or smaller ones
down here, whatever they are, when you
click on the settings, there's a little
button at the bottom that says share as
template. And when you click on that, it
basically just shoots off this prompt to
your bot that says create a template of
yourself that I can share with somebody
else. And it says, okay, I'll make a
sharable copy. I will read my memories.
I'll read my skills. I'll read my
routines and my plugins. And then I will
keep some things and leave out any
personal details and unused connectors.
So it basically just packages this up
almost like a plug-in or like uh like a
claude skill or any of these other
things. It's just a template that other
people could then use and you can look
at the details before you publish it.
You can see the actual context that it
gets. So it's a daily AI news scout. It
searches X for new models. I'll actually
publish this one and put it in my free
school community with this video if you
guys want to grab it. It's pretty easy
to make, but I'll still put this one in
here. Anyways, then it says, you know, I
send a short evening ClickUp DM with
that day's API spend. And then there's a
few memories in here. So, this agent is
the owner's daily AI new scout every day
at 6 p.m. Central. Search X for new
models, lab drama, and new tools, and
trending GitHub repos. Then send a
concise summary to ClickUp. Then we also
have this memory. Each daily AI digest
must include how many X API credits that
run costs, plus the remaining balance.
And then it should keep each run between
30 to 50. So now, if I like this, I
could go ahead and publish this. So if I
don't like it, I can say, "Hey, take
this out or take that, you know, put
that into the actual bot template that I
want to share." And then you can publish
it. So this is going to actually publish
this bot, which I can go ahead and copy
the link. And let's say I put this in a
community or put this in, you know, on X
or something like that, which a lot of
people will be doing. This bot is now
available. And you can go ahead and add
this to your own Grockbot. So here is
one by Matt and you can see this is a
it's called loops. So it's a generalized
engineering outer loop. sits above
coding agents, uses Pstack as reference,
writes SLGO style prompts, blah blah
blah, and all I have to do is literally
just click add to Grotbot, and then it
opens up Grockbot, and then it basically
just gives us same thing. We get to look
at the context and the integrations to
make sure there's nothing like super
malicious in here or anything. You
always want to be safe when you're
downloading or installing anything from
the internet because you don't know what
people's intent on the back end might
be. We can look through the memories. We
can look through all this and if we feel
good about it, then we can go ahead and
add this bot and it spins up a new one.
You can see it just created one called
loops and it says, "Hi loops, please
install these plugins and write your
memories." So, as we know, it's going to
connect things like GitHub and Pstack.
We would obviously have to authenticate
in ourselves. We're not going to be able
to authenticate into Matt's GitHub or
whatever else he has as the integrations
and connectors, but there are some
things that wouldn't come with this bot.
for example, if he had certain custom
code that was being stored locally or if
you know there was other like env like
environment variables or anything else
that was stored like that that wouldn't
get packaged over as part of this
template. So there's still going to be a
little bit of setup. It's not exactly
immediately like just plug-andplay. It's
it's right away ready to go. You have to
connect your own things. You can add a
little bit of your own flavor. It's
going to ask you and walk you through
what that looks like, but then you're
good to go. So just one other example to
show you. I did the same exact thing
with studio. I went to the settings. I
clicked on share as template. And this
one had a few other things, right? It
had different memories. It had different
skills. It had no routines here,
different types of plugins. And now we
have the same thing which we can go
ahead and view the details on. We can
see the context. We can see the
memories. And we can also see the skills
because this one had skills whereas the
other one didn't. So if you do have an
agent that has a ton of useful skills,
you can go ahead and share those with
people. You could also maybe even
consider selling them. Now, I'm not
saying that's something that is going to
make you millions. I'm not saying that
that's really a viable business model,
but I'm saying people will be selling
skills and people will be selling
Grockbot templates. I can almost
guarantee it. People sell nodend
workflows, people sell cloud skills,
people sell GitHub repos, people will
sell almost anything. So don't be
surprised if you see people out there on
X or on LinkedIn selling Grockbot
templates. If you want to try to maybe,
you know, have a community where you
sell a bunch of these inside of it, that
might be viable as well. But the point
I'm trying to make here is this is
something you can do. You can share this
with your friends, your communities,
your team. If you, you know, if you all
want to have different bots and you can
share those around. Um, but if you're
looking for a very specific type of
automation in here or skill, then maybe
do a little bit of research first and
see if there's already a Grockbot
template out there that exists that you
could just pull in real quick and sort
of customize to make your own. So, that
is Grockbot templates. Okay. Okay, so
now that we've talked about all that,
let me talk about what could this
actually look like as a service offering
if you're already running some sort of
AI agency or maybe you want to run some
sort of AI agency or maybe you just want
to do Grockbot setups for people because
I think right now that's a very viable
option. You know, we've seen people do
chatbt education workshops and summits.
We've seen the same thing with Claude.
Um we've seen the same thing with Claude
Code and Co-work and now it's going to
happen again with Grockbot for a short
window. So the way I see it is it's a
good foot in the door to build trust.
And what I mean by that is I think a lot
of us are in a spot where when you're
building your AI agency, you want to get
to the point where you've got clients on
retainer. Whether that starts out at 5K
a month and then maybe works up to 10 or
when my agency was doing 20K a month
minimum retainers, you're in a good spot
because you've got consistent cash flow
coming in. And a lot of people that I've
talked to, a lot of my students and
stuff, they want to start here. And it's
so so hard to start here, which is why
it feels like it's hard to get business
and it's hard to close the sales. So, I
want to talk about real quick the AI
service ladder and how I see this
Grockbot setup offering fitting into
that stack. So, like I said, it's a
ladder. The retainers are pretty much at
the top of that ladder and I think that
you have to earn each rung. So, you
really usually start down here with free
work. You move up to like hourly and
education consulting. You then can move
up to things like paid audits to get
your foot in the door for these bigger
projects that could be anywhere from
1,000 to upwards of 10,000. And then I
see it as after you've delivered your
first project for that business and they
really like it, you've proven the value,
then you go in there and pitch the
retainer after you've already proven
that you work well and you can help grow
their business. It's very hard to get
someone to sign up for a subscription,
which essentially this is a very, very
expensive subscription before they've
known you and have any trust with you
unless, and this is the thing here,
unless you have a lot of proof already.
So, for example, when we were selling
$20,000 a month retainers minimum to
work with us, it was because we had so
much proof and also because we had um
the constraint for us was supply,
meaning we had so many leads coming in
that we wanted to keep raising the
barrier to entry to see that, you know,
the people that want to work with us are
serious. They're willing to pay this
retainer and they've already got a
bigger budget. So, those are some things
to think about, but really, you want to
start with the free work and you want to
get as much experience as you can so
then you can keep working your way up
the ladder. That's kind of the way that
I think about this, the AI service
ladder of offerings. So, where this
really fits in, I think, is hourly
education and consulting or maybe you're
able to package this into some sort of
project like $5,000 to get you and your
team set up with Grockbot, everyone
personally. And the way that you
actually can start to pitch this is you
have to be your own proof. Meaning you
have to have done what we did in this
course but also taking it farther where
you've got teams, you've got your
executive team, you've got all your
operators and you have so many skills
and automations built into it that you
can truly say, you know, I'm one person
right now or I'm a very small team with
a few people, but we're able to do this
much output because if I'm on vacation
for a week, all of this stuff continues
to run with me, keeps my business
numbers updated, keeps all the stuff
going. And that is where you achieve a
lot of just a lot of leverage, a lot of
unlock potential. And if you're able to
say, "This is how this has explicitly
helped my business." I will help you set
up the exact same thing. That's such a
better offer than showing a bunch of
different cool websites or a portfolio
of things that you've built that isn't
as relevant to them. If you are the
living proof of what you can provide and
the risk to them is much smaller because
it's not $1,000 project or a retainer.
It's literally, hey, this might take us
5 hours this weekend, right? You pay me
my hourly rate of let's just say 100
bucks an hour. That's not very risky to
them. You know, maybe they waste waste 5
hours of their time, 500 bucks, which to
a business usually isn't too much. The
time is actually what they're more
concerned about typically. But worst
case scenario, they walk away with a
Grockbot and having learned a bunch of
stuff about how AI works and how to work
with different agents. And best case
scenario for you, they love that. They
now trust you. They have a relationship
with you. And it's like, hey, would you
like me to do an audit of your business
to help you figure out where are even
better opportunities to build more
Grockbots, or would you like me to do a
whole training workshop for your entire
team now and have everyone set up
Grockbots? This trust layer right here
gets your foot in the door for these
bigger projects and these bigger
retainers, but it has to come first,
especially when you're getting started.
And then from there, you can use
Grockbots to help you do this more,
right? Obviously run your own business,
but help you maybe write more cold
outreach copy and stuff like that. And
when you're teaching them, you want to
go through this AI operating system, the
context, the connections, the
capabilities, and the cadence because
coming in with a framework like this
makes you seem way more credible. It
makes you makes them feel like you've
done this before and you really know
what you're talking about and you like
you're the guy to get it done or the
girl to get it done. Coming in with a
framework builds trust immediately. So,
steal this framework. It's fine. You can
use this because I think it's a really
good way to demonstrate what you're
actually building here. And then, like I
said earlier, you can use something like
Clay. You know, there's a connector
inside of Grockbot. You can see that
it's it's working on these images here.
I recorded this part in the middle, but
there's a connector in here for Clay.
And what Clay does is it helps you
enrich people and companies, run AI
research agents. It helps you find B2B
data better. You just have to be very
clear before you hop into Clay. Who is
your person that you're targeting? What
is their pain point? And how do you
promise to solve that pain? I call that
the three Ps of um AI monetization. So
if you have those things, the person,
the pain, and the promise, and that's in
the context inside of your Grogbot
system, and then you give it the
connection of Clay to find all those
leads, enrich all those leads, write all
the outreach messages, and maybe even
connected to Clay to schedule them out
or connected Gmail instantly, whatever
you want to do. And then you pair those
things with cadence and capabilities.
You're maybe having a Grockbot that's
every single day sending out 50 cold
emails for you every day. And then you
have a different agent that's analyzing
them, um, giving you a report and also
finding out where are things going wrong
and fixing the copy, fixing these
workflows, fixing the skills, so that
every day this cold outreach system is
just getting better and better. And if
you want to see a little bit more about
this, I did a video with Claude and
Clay, which I'll tag right up here. You
can go ahead and check that out. It's
going to be very similar, except for
obviously instead of using Claude as the
orchestrator, you're going to be using
Grockbot and maybe different Grockbot
agents to orchestrate Clay. But the
theory is going to be very similar on
how that works. But anyways, I really
think there's a big opportunity here,
especially when you think about this
ladder, how you start here, you move up
to here, you do Grockbot trainings, you
do audits, you get into these retainers,
and that's where you really start to
just be able to have better
testimonials, get way more um, you know,
referrals from your clients because
you've already proven value. It's all
about building trust and building the
relationship early and then on the back
end, you can really start to do some
cool stuff. And if you guys want to
learn a lot more about like AI
monetization, building a business,
clients, outreach, all that type of
stuff, then check out this playlist,
which I'll tag right over here or right
over here. And it's just a full
breakdown of a bunch of stuff that I've
learned through my journey of building
my agency and working with clients. So
anyways, hope to see you guys in some of
those videos over there. That's going to
do it for today. Thanks everyone.